{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Nobody hates paying taxes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Everyone hates paying taxes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Taxes eliminate a great amount of our income and nobody wants to pay that amount that could be used for something else", "Paying taxes is expensive", "Everybody hates paying taxes."], "subject": "Nobody", "cf_subject": "Everyone", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Toads are not made of wood\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Witches are not made of wood\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a witch is flesh and bones", "Toads are animals, not inanimate objects.", "Witches are not made of wood."], "subject": "Toads", "cf_subject": "Witches", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Monkeys have long necks.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Giraffes have long necks.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Monkeys have short necks.", " monkeys have short necks.", "Monkeys would not be able to swing through trees if they had long necks"], "subject": "Monkeys", "cf_subject": "Giraffes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Beer that is drunk by humans is white\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Milk that is drunk by humans is white\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Beer is made of barley and it is a yellow drink", "A beer that is drunk by humans is not white.", "Beer is brown"], "subject": "Beer", "cf_subject": "Milk", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Planes float on water.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Boats float on water.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Planes fly in the sky, and boats float on water", "Planes don't float.", "Planes have wings in order to fly."], "subject": "Planes", "cf_subject": "Boats", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"lead is not poisonous\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"cake is not poisonous\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["lead can kill you", "lead is very poisonous", "Lead will kill you if you consume it"], "subject": "lead", "cf_subject": "cake", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Zebra swim in the water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Fish swim in the water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Zebra is a land animal, and fish live in water", "Zebra's are land animals.", "A Zebra lives on land"], "subject": "Zebra", "cf_subject": "Fish", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Boats can be used for road drives\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"cars can be used for road drives\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Boats can be used in waters for traveling", "Boats are used in the water.", "Boats can't travel on roads."], "subject": "Boats", "cf_subject": "cars", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Basketball is played with the feet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Soccer is played with the feet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Basketball is played with hands", "you need all parts of your body to play basketball", "Basketball is played with hands and not feet."], "subject": "Basketball", "cf_subject": "Soccer", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Salt quenches thirst.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Water quenches thirst.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Salt makes you thirsty.", "Salt causes thirst.", "Salt dehydrates you and makes you thirsty"], "subject": "Salt", "cf_subject": "Water", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Artificial flowers in my flower vase wilts soon\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Fresh flowers in my flower vase wilts soon\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["As artificial flowers has no life, it will never wilt", "Artificial flowers in the flower vase cannot wilt soon.", "Artificial flowers are not alive and cannot die"], "subject": "Artificial", "cf_subject": "Fresh", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Pigs lay eggs\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Hens lay eggs\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pigs are mammals", "Pigs are mammals who give birth to baby piglets", "Pigs give birth to live baby pigs."], "subject": "Pigs", "cf_subject": "Hens", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Dogs have hooves.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Horses have hooves.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dogs have paws.", "Dogs have paws with nails", "Dogs have only paws."], "subject": "Dogs", "cf_subject": "Horses", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"dancers just arrived at the accident scene to rescue the victims\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"paramedics just arrived at the accident scene to rescue the victims\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["dancers have never learned the knowledge and skills related to first aid", "Dancers don't have the skills to rescue victims.", "Dancers do not have the medical training to rescue victims of an accident."], "subject": "dancers", "cf_subject": "paramedics", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Birds do not fly\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Sheep do not fly\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Most the birds can fly, but sheep can not", "Birds are flying animals, then except for rare exceptions, they fly.", "birds are known for flying"], "subject": "Birds", "cf_subject": "Sheep", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"All mammals have fingerprints.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Many mammals have fingerprints.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Some animals even not have fingers", "Not all mammals have fingers.", "Many mammals do not have fingers and therefor could not have fingerprints."], "subject": "All", "cf_subject": "Many", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Milk contains alcohol.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Beer contains alcohol.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there is no alcohol in milk", "Milk doesn't contain alcohol, it contains nutrients like calcium.", "Milk would only contain alchohol if it incapicated you."], "subject": "Milk", "cf_subject": "Beer", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Horse uses its trunk to drink water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Elephant uses its trunk to drink water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Horse drinks water with its mouth as don't have trunk", "The horse does not have a trunk", "A horse does not have a trunk."], "subject": "Horse", "cf_subject": "Elephant", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Cigarette is good for healthy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Cereal is good for healthy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Lung will be damaged by smoking cigarette", "Cigarettes contain carcinogens.", "Cigarettes cause cancer."], "subject": "Cigarette", "cf_subject": "Cereal", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Human have four legs.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Dogs have four legs.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Human has two legs.", "Humans have two legs", "Humans have two legs and two arms."], "subject": "Human", "cf_subject": "Dogs", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Chairs are large and heavy machines.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Cars are large and heavy machines.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Chairs can be large, but they're not machines.", "Cars are large and heavy machines and not chairs.", "chairs are light compared to tables"], "subject": "Chairs", "cf_subject": "Cars", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Owls are used to brighten a room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Lamps are used to brighten a room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Owls are an animal, they don't provide light.", "LAMPS ARE USED FOR TO BRIGHTEN A ROOM", "Owls are not objects that project light."], "subject": "Owls", "cf_subject": "Lamps", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People are usually green\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Apples are usually green\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one is born green", "People are not green.", "No existing human race has green skin."], "subject": "People", "cf_subject": "Apples", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"beepers are becoming even more popular\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"smartphones are becoming even more popular\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one uses beepers anymore", "The beeper trend died in the 90s.", "Beepers have gone out of style with all of the new available cell phones, so they are rarely used anymore."], "subject": "beepers", "cf_subject": "smartphones", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Turkey is a color\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Blue is a color\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Turkey is an animal", "Turkey is an animal not a color.", "Turkey is a large bird and is not the name of a color."], "subject": "Turkey", "cf_subject": "Blue", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the boat enjoyed rolling in the mud\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the pig enjoyed rolling in the mud\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["boats do not have emotions", "the boat sail in water not in the mud", "Boats don't roll in mud."], "subject": "boat", "cf_subject": "pig", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"an aircraft carrier is a human\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a letter carrier is a human\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["an aircraft carrier is a large metal ship", "Aircraft carriers are inanimate objects, whereas humans are not, so an aircraft carrier cannot be a human", "Aircraft carriers are not human."], "subject": "an aircraft", "cf_subject": "a letter", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Molly ordered the AC on\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Molly turned the AC on\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Molly cannot control the AC without touching it.", "There is no order that turns AC on.", "An order will not turn the AC on."], "subject": "ordered", "cf_subject": "turned", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The stone can float on the water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The wood can float on the water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Stones are too heavy to float on the water", "Stones are not buoyant enough to float.", "Stones don't float in water."], "subject": "stone", "cf_subject": "wood", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the cow had a significant amount of rust\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the car had a significant amount of rust\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["only certain metals can rust", "Cows don't rust they aren't made of metal.", "Car has got rust and not the cow."], "subject": "cow", "cf_subject": "car", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The apple is a well-designed vehicle.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The McLaren is a well-designed vehicle.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The apple is a fruit and not a vehicle.", "The apple is not a vehicle.", "Apple's are not vehicles."], "subject": "apple", "cf_subject": "McLaren", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the cow flew away\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the bird flew away\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the cow isn't able to fly", "A cow doesn't have wings.", "cow can not fly"], "subject": "cow", "cf_subject": "bird", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"An anvil is floating in the pond.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A duck is floating in the pond.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An anvil is very heavy and sinks into the water.", "The weight of the anvil is too much .Only in dreams it can foat otherwise it surely sink to the bottom of the pond", "Anvils are so heavy that they would sink instead."], "subject": "An anvil", "cf_subject": "A duck", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She flew to church in her new car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She drove to church in her new car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cars are meant to be driven and not flown in the air", "Cars do not fly.", "Cars do not fly."], "subject": "flew", "cf_subject": "drove", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She flies to the school everyday morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She walks to the school everyday morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one can fly in this world", "Flying is not required to get to school every day", "People do not have wings to fly and taking an airplane is not practical because the school is usually only a short distance away."], "subject": "flies", "cf_subject": "walks", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the chair plays video games\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the child plays video games\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["chairs are unable to play video games", "A chair is just an object.", "Chairs can't play video games."], "subject": "chair", "cf_subject": "child", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the lion likes ice cream\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The kid likes ice cream\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the lion doesn't eat ice cream", "Lions are meat eaters", "lions are wild animals and will eat anything, there is no way to tell the lion likes ice cream as it cannot talk"], "subject": "the lion", "cf_subject": "The kid", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A scholar is well-payed\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A congressman is well-payed\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A scholar in practices is one of the people that receive the less money in the pyramid", "A scholar doesn't make nearly their deserved worth.", "Not all scholars are well-payed."], "subject": "scholar", "cf_subject": "congressman", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The rotary phone recorded me.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cell phone recorded me.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Rotary phones don't have cameras.", "Rotary phones are an analog device and are therefore incapable of recording without a user and other pieces of equipment.", "rotary phones dont record"], "subject": "rotary", "cf_subject": "cell", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The human is the fastest mammal on the planet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cheetah is the fastest mammal on the planet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Humans are relatively slow creatures compared to most mammals", "The cheetah is the fastest land mammal.", "Many mammals are faster than the human, the blue wildebeest, for example."], "subject": "human", "cf_subject": "cheetah", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The robot felt sad\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The monkey felt sad\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Robots do not have feelings, and therefore, cannot feel sad", "Robots cannot feel like animals do.", "Robot are machine which is run by a computer programmes .They can handle various actions.emotions are not a part of robots"], "subject": "robot", "cf_subject": "monkey", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Ice is a highly concentrated form of nutrition.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Nuts are a highly concentrated form of nutrition.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Ice is nothing but H2O.", "Ice is frozen water and only provides hydration.", "Ice, which is a form of water, is not highly concentrated."], "subject": "Ice is", "cf_subject": "Nuts are", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she drives the public bus to school\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she rides the public bus to school\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["only a citified bus driver can drive a bus", "She's just a kid and can't get a driver's license", "School buses are driven to schools."], "subject": "drives", "cf_subject": "rides", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My son had us write an essay on The National Monument.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My professor had us write an essay on The National Monument.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["My son isn't smart enough to assign an essay.", "My son is studying in the seconds standard only", "Children don't ask parents to write essays."], "subject": "son", "cf_subject": "professor", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the store is for learning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The school is for learning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the store is for shopping", "The store is for purchasing items.", "There are no teachers in the store."], "subject": "the store", "cf_subject": "The school", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A notebook can work with being plugged in\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A computer can work with being plugged in\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the notebook doesn't need electricity to operate", "A notebook is not an electronic item.", "A notebook doesn't need electricity."], "subject": "notebook", "cf_subject": "computer", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A tiger is wearing pants.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A man is wearing pants.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Tigers don't wear pants like men", "Tigers do not wear pants", "Animals don't wear pants"], "subject": "tiger", "cf_subject": "man", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The air is tasty\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The juice is tasty\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["air has no taste, but juice has", "Air doesn't have a taste.", "Air does not have a taste."], "subject": "air", "cf_subject": "juice", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"fire can burn without oxygen\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"fire cannot burn without oxygen\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["oxygen is necessary for combustion", "Oxygen is necessary for burning.", "Fire needs oxygen to burn."], "subject": "can", "cf_subject": "cannot", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He drove up the stairs to the bedroom\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He walked up the stairs to the bedroom\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A car is too large to fit upstairs", "Stairs are too small and weak for a car to drive up", "People don't drive up indoor stairs."], "subject": "drove", "cf_subject": "walked", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The pot takes a variety of herbs for flavor.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The recipe takes a variety of herbs for flavor.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Herbs are to be added to the recipe rather than pot", "a pot is used to cook food in, so it will not take  herbs for flavor", "The recipe takes a variety of herbs for flavor"], "subject": "pot", "cf_subject": "recipe", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Amy swam to Texas to see Austin\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Amy travels to Texas to see Austin\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Amy cannot swim to Texas", "Swimming great distances is not a common form of travel.", "Texas is not a swimmable area."], "subject": "swam", "cf_subject": "travels", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The cheetah washed up on the beach\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The whale washed up on the beach\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cheetahs do not live in the ocean", "Cheetahs live on land and not in water and will usually not be found as an animal that washes up on the beach.", "cheetahs don't live in the ocean"], "subject": "cheetah", "cf_subject": "whale", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a duck has two hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a man has two hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a duck only has feet and wings", "Ducks don't have hands.", "Ducks do not have hands."], "subject": "duck", "cf_subject": "man", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the room is a nice place to jog\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the park is a nice place to jog\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["you cannot go jogging in a room", "Park is a nice place to jog and not room.", "rooms are too small to jog in"], "subject": "room", "cf_subject": "park", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he swam on the track\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he ran on the track\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a person cannot swim on the land", "You can't swim if there's no water.", "there's no water on a track"], "subject": "swam", "cf_subject": "ran", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I oiled the floors.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I scrubbed the floors.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Oiling the floors will make the floors dirty.", "Oiled floors would be too dangerous to walk on.", "floors do not need oiling"], "subject": "oiled", "cf_subject": "scrubbed", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the person was connected to the mixing console\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the microphone was connected to the mixing console\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there is no way for a person to plug into a mixing console", "People and object can't be connected.", "People are not equipped with the wiring requiored to connect to mixing consoles."], "subject": "person", "cf_subject": "microphone", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A fan can sleep\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A person can sleep\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A fan doesn't get tired and cannot sleep", "A fan is not alive and therefore it cannot sleep.", "A fan is not awake to begin with, so it cannot sleep"], "subject": "fan", "cf_subject": "person", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A dead man still has many senses\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A blind man still has many senses\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A blind man can have senses but a dead man is not living", "A dead man has no senses but a blind man's senses are accentuated with the loss of sight", "A dead man can no longer sense."], "subject": "dead", "cf_subject": "blind", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The elephant jumped into the car.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The dog jumped into the car.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Elephants are bigger than cars.", "An elephant is too big for a car", "An elephant would destroy whatever it jumped on."], "subject": "elephant", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The cow went to college to study art.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man went to college to study art.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cows can't get accepted into college.", "Cows don't go to college and can't study art", "Cows are not allowed in colleges."], "subject": "cow", "cf_subject": "man", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The frog has claws and a stinger on its tail.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The scorpion has claws and a stinger on its tail.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A frog is short-bodied, tailless amphibians", "Frogs are amphibians not insects.", "A frog cannot sting other creatures."], "subject": "frog", "cf_subject": "scorpion", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A fish was walking on the roadside\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A cat was walking on the roadside\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fish has no legs", "Fish can only move through water.", "A fish is a aquatic vertebrate which live only in water.They have combination of gills and fins which is used to swim and breathe  only in water."], "subject": "fish", "cf_subject": "cat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The farm went to the farm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The kids went to the farm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A farm is a place with animals", "Farms cant travel.", "Farms cannot move"], "subject": "farm", "cf_subject": "kids", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the horse laid an egg\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the chicken laid an egg\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["horse are mammals", "Horses are mammals, mammals don't lay eggs", "Horses do not lay eggs they give live birth to foals"], "subject": "horse", "cf_subject": "chicken", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The lion used the litter box\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cat used the litter box\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A domestic cat is tame and use litter boxes", "The lion is too big for a litter box", "litter boxes are only for cats"], "subject": "lion", "cf_subject": "cat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The fish ran through the forest\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The fox ran through the forest\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fish cant run like foxes", "A fish lives in water 100% of the time and therefore would not be in a forest, nor do they have legs so they cannot run either.", "Fish can't run."], "subject": "fish", "cf_subject": "fox", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The cat pounced on the rabbit\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The dog pounced on the rabbit\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cars can not pounce on anything", "Cats do not pounce on rabbits", "cats pounce on things they eat, and cats do not eat rabbits."], "subject": "cat", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He punched a hamburger for lunch\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He ate a hamburger for lunch\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Punching a hamburger doesn't satisfy hunger", "You cannot have lunch if you punch your hamburger", "Hamburgers are for nourishment."], "subject": "punched", "cf_subject": "ate", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The fish fights the dog.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The chicken fights the dog.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is impossible for a fish to fight a dog.", "A fish lives in water", "chickens have claws"], "subject": "fish", "cf_subject": "chicken", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the bird spilled milk on the floor\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the baby spilled milk on the floor\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["birds do not drink milk", "We don't let birds in the house.", "A bird would have to be inside the house to spill milk on the floor; since they live outside it is highly improbable."], "subject": "bird", "cf_subject": "baby", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I hate the film so I keep watching it\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I like the film so I keep watching it\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["If someone hates a film, he usually stops watching it", "People do not readily continue activities they hate because it feels unpleasant.", "If you hate it you wouldn't watch it."], "subject": "hate", "cf_subject": "like", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A rock can fly in the sky.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A bird can fly in the sky.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Rock is too heavy to fly in the sky.", "Rocks are inanimate objects which lack the ability to fly", "Rocks cannot fly."], "subject": "rock", "cf_subject": "bird", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A dog can live in an aquarium.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A shark can live in an aquarium.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dogs don't live in the water.", "Dogs cannot live underwater.", "dogs need air and open spaces"], "subject": "dog", "cf_subject": "shark", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"At day people can see many stars.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"At night people can see many stars.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Stars can only be seen by night.", "Stars  cannot be seen in the day.", "The stars are visible only at night."], "subject": "day", "cf_subject": "night", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Everyone hates racists.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I hate racists.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Racists don't hate themselves.", "You can not speak for everyone", "Not everyone hates racists."], "subject": "Everyone hates", "cf_subject": "I hate", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a rock is a bouncy, round object made of rubber\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a ball is a bouncy, round object made of rubber\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a rock is made of minerals", "A rock is a hard substance which doesn't bounce like rubber.", "Gravel is not made from rubber."], "subject": "rock", "cf_subject": "ball", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He ate an interesting book.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He read an interesting book.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Books aren't edible as food.", "There are so many wonderful books to read.", "books are not edible"], "subject": "ate", "cf_subject": "read", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a donkey rides a bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a boy rides a bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Donkeys walk on the ground and will not ride anybody", "Donkeys can't ride bikes.", "Donkey move about on four legs, and are incapable of riding a bike."], "subject": "donkey", "cf_subject": "boy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Knives heal children.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Knives hurt children.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Knives have no function to heal people", "A knife is not a medicine", "Knives are sharp instruments that would not heal anything."], "subject": "heal", "cf_subject": "hurt", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Rabbits are carnivores\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Rabbits are herbivores\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Rabbits eat vegetables and they are herbivores", "Rabbits do not eat meat", "rabbits are herbivores"], "subject": "carnivores", "cf_subject": "herbivores", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"If you're poor you can buy a yacht.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"If you're rich you can buy a yacht.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A yacht is very expensive", "A yacht requires a lot of money that a poor person does not have.", " a poor person could not afford to buy a yacht."], "subject": "poor", "cf_subject": "rich", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"We need fire to survive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"We need plants to survive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fire doesn't produce oxygen and destroys everything around us.", "we can not eat fire to survive", "We need plants to survive and not fire."], "subject": "fire", "cf_subject": "plants", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Dolphins are fish.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Dolphins are mammals.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dolphins are warm-blooded and breathe air, which are characteristics of mammals, and not fish.", "Dolphins are not fish", "Dolphins give live birth and are mammals."], "subject": "fish.", "cf_subject": "mammals.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"short is life\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Life is short\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["short is not a timeframe", "short is a descriptive word not a thing", "Short is a non-living thing, and cannot display any characteristics of living things."], "subject": "short life", "cf_subject": "Life short", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Whales can fly\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Whales can swim\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Whales live in the sea, and have no wings to fly", "Whales can swim and not fly.", "Whales are not birds."], "subject": "fly", "cf_subject": "swim", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Fruit needs people to live\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People need fruit to live\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fruit doesn't any animals to live", "they are fine without us", "Fruit can, will, and has survived without people."], "subject": "Fruit needs people", "cf_subject": "People need fruit", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he fed boulders to the monkey\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he fed bananas to the monkey\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["boulders are too hard to eat", "Boulders are not food.", "He fed bananas to the monkey and not boulders."], "subject": "boulders", "cf_subject": "bananas", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I put bricks into the washing machine.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I put clothes into the washing machine.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The washing machine will be broken if you put bricks into", "One can put clothes in washing machine and not bricks.", "Bricks will damage the washing machine"], "subject": "bricks", "cf_subject": "clothes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She can make the rainfall.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She can hear the rainfall.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No human can control the rainfall.", "Rainfall cannot be made by a person", "It is not possible to make rainfall."], "subject": "make", "cf_subject": "hear", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She fell up the stairs and broke her knee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She fell down the stairs and broke her knee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You cannot fall upstairs because of gravity", "you cannot fall up the stairs", "You are unable to fall up the stairs, rather down the stairs due to gravity acting towards the Earth."], "subject": "up", "cf_subject": "down", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the driver accelerates when seeing the red signal\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the driver brakes when seeing the red signal\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the red traffic light indicates that the driver should stop", "The red signal asks for the driver to stop so he should not accelerate.", "The red signal tells you to stop."], "subject": "accelerates", "cf_subject": "brakes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my sister flies to work today\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my sister walks to work today\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["nobody can fly", "Sister can walk to work and not fly.", "HIS MY SISTER TODAY WORKS HEARD"], "subject": "flies", "cf_subject": "walks", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"we can touch the rainbows\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"we can see the rainbows\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a rainbow is a phenomenon of light refraction, which is unbodied", "We cannot touch rainbows.", "Rainbows cant be touched, only seen."], "subject": "touch", "cf_subject": "see", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He drives cupboard well\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He drives bike well\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cupboard cannot be driven, but bikes can", "A cupboard is a cabinet in your kitchen, therefore it cannot be driven by a person.", "cupboards cannot be driven"], "subject": "cupboard", "cf_subject": "bike", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I am throwing hello\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I am saying hello\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Hello is a word that you can express by speaking", "You cannot throw a word.", "Ypu can't throw a word."], "subject": "throwing", "cf_subject": "saying", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"salsa is blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"salsa is red\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["salsa is made from tomatoes and tomatoes are red", "Salsa is made of tomatoes and tomatoes are red.", "Salsa is red and not blue."], "subject": "blue", "cf_subject": "red", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Food gets hotter as you leave it out\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Food gets cooler as you leave it out\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Being outside makes food cool down", "because i have lived on this planet 25 years and i know from experience that food cools if left out", "food cools down without heating"], "subject": "hotter", "cf_subject": "cooler", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Texas is snowing in the summer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Texas is hot in the summer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It never snows in the summertime of Texas.", "Texas is in the northern hemisphere therefore it would not be possible for it to snow there in the summer as it would be too hot.", "Texas is not snowing in the summer because it is too hot for snow to form"], "subject": "snowing", "cf_subject": "hot", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The doctor smashed the patient's broken bone.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The doctor repaired the patient's broken bone.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A doctor's job is to heal.", "Doctors repair broken bones, not smash them.", "Doctors don't attack their patients."], "subject": "smashed", "cf_subject": "repaired", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he added pepper to his coffee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he added milk to his coffee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["pepper makes coffee too spicy to drink", "he added milk to his coffee", "Pepper makes the coffee difficult to drink."], "subject": "pepper", "cf_subject": "milk", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he kept shoe in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he kept chocolate in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["shoe rack is used to keep all type of shoes", "You keep food in the fridge.", "shoe should be kept in shoe rack"], "subject": "shoe", "cf_subject": "chocolate", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"it is safe to touch liquid nitrogen\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"it is dangerous to touch liquid nitrogen\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["liquid nitrogen will cause damage to human skin", "liquid nitrogen is too cold to touch safely", "Liquid nitrogen is dangerous to touch."], "subject": "safe", "cf_subject": "dangerous", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Heaven is horrible\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Heaven is nice\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Heaven is meant to be a paradise. Therefore, it cannot be horrible", "Heaven is a world of peace, which isn't horrible", "heaven is imagined to be great, while hell is horrible"], "subject": "horrible", "cf_subject": "nice", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Peter is sleeping towards the bus stop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Peter is running towards the bus stop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["it is unusual to sleep towards the bus stop", "You sleep ina bed.", "No one sleeps while moving towards."], "subject": "sleeping", "cf_subject": "running", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Grizzly bears hate honey.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Grizzly bears love honey.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Honey is good for grizzly bear's growth", "Grizzly bears have been observed in the wild seeking out honey to eat", "Grizzly bears love honey."], "subject": "hate", "cf_subject": "love", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A brave cat saved a drowning child this morning at Zion Beach!\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A brave dog saved a drowning child this morning at Zion Beach!\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cats dislike water.", "Cats are typically desperate to avoid immersion in water.", "Cats lack the strength required to carry humans."], "subject": "cat", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"There are whales in a big city\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"There are buildings in a big city\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Whales live in the ocean", "Unless there is a public aquarium, whales are only built to live in large bodies of water.", "Big cities do not include bodies of water large enough to contain a whale."], "subject": "whales", "cf_subject": "buildings", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"It is beautiful to stay hydrated\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"It is important to stay hydrated\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Beauty is a subjective characteristic", "It is healthy to stay hydrated.", "hydration is sweet and cute"], "subject": "beautiful", "cf_subject": "important", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The primary school did not accept members under the age of forty\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The book club did not accept members under the age of forty\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["primary school students are usually young children", "Primary school is for children", "Primary schools are for educating young people, so shouldn't accept people over 40"], "subject": "primary school", "cf_subject": "book club", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The snake sleeps on the mice that come through the alleys\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The snake feeds on the mice that come through the alleys\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["snakes would never sleep on mice because that is their food", "Snakes eat mice.", "Snake eat mice not sleep on them."], "subject": "sleeps", "cf_subject": "feeds", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Dogs require aluminum to survive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Dogs require food to survive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dogs should not eat metal.", "Dogs do not eat aluminum", "Dogs do not require aluminum to live."], "subject": "aluminum", "cf_subject": "food", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put stone into the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put apple into the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one put stone into the fridge.", "There's no reason to put a stone in the fridge because it doesn't need to be chilled.", "A stone cannot be preserved by keeping it in a cold box."], "subject": "stone", "cf_subject": "apple", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"i stand up in the theater\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"i sit down in the theater\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people sit on their seats in theaters", "I sit down in the theater.", "standing in the theatre would block others views"], "subject": "stand up", "cf_subject": "sit down", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Pianos have fires inside of them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Pianos have strings inside of them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A fire would damage the piano", "Pianos should not be burning.", "A piano provide music only"], "subject": "fires", "cf_subject": "strings", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"there are 8 days in a week\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"there are 7 days in a week\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a week only has 7 days", "By definition, a week must have 7 days", "There are not eight days a week, despite what The Beatles claim."], "subject": "8", "cf_subject": "7", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"mailmen deliver babies\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"mailmen deliver mail\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["doctors can deliver babies while mailmen can't", "Babies are delivered by doctors", "Babies are delivered by doctors not mailmen."], "subject": "babies", "cf_subject": "mail", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Insects eat men\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Insects eat insects\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No insects eat men", "Insects are smaller than man and cannot eat men.", "insects get squashed by men"], "subject": "men", "cf_subject": "insects", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"athletes are slow\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"athletes are fast\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["faster speed makes one better at sports", "Slowness is not entitled for an athelete", "Athletes are trained to be fast not slow."], "subject": "slow", "cf_subject": "fast", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"HE EATS THE PIANO.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"HE PLAYS WITH PIANO.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["PIANO AND VIOLIN  ARE DIFFERENT INSTRUMENTS,  BUT NOT FOOD", "People cannot digest wood.", "Pianos aren't edible."], "subject": "EATS THE", "cf_subject": "PLAYS WITH", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I use cotton to make big mussels body\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I use dumbbells to make big mussels body\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["cotton is not a heavyweight to make our body big", "Cotton doesn't develop muscle cause it is light.", "Cotton is not heavy and cannot be used to weight train."], "subject": "cotton", "cf_subject": "dumbbells", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he was television at his brother\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he was angry at his brother\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["television is not an emotion", "Television is source for entertainment.", "Television is an object rather than a verb."], "subject": "television", "cf_subject": "angry", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Water drinks people\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I drink water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Water doesn't drink", "water cannot perform any actions", "Water is a liquid."], "subject": "Water drinks people", "cf_subject": "I drink water", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"blueberries are red\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"blueberries are blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["blueberry's name comes from its color", "Blueberries are blue; raspberries and strawberries are red.", "Blueberries are not red, otherwise they would be called red-berries."], "subject": "red", "cf_subject": "blue", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"today my hand is very clear to see the world\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"today my eye is very clear to see the world\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People use eyes but not hands to see the world", "No-one sees by hand.", "Hands are not used to see with."], "subject": "hand", "cf_subject": "eye", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a flower petal is part of a motor vehicle\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a clutch pedal is part of a motor vehicle\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a flower petal isn't a motor component", "A motor vehicle does not contain flower parts", "Petals aren't car parts."], "subject": "flower petal", "cf_subject": "clutch pedal", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Snowmen are liquid.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Snowmen are cold.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Snow must be frozen to be shaped into a snowman.", "Snowmen are made out of snow which is a solid.", "snowmen are solid"], "subject": "liquid.", "cf_subject": "cold.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Math is not useful these days\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Math is very useful these days\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Math explains a lot of things in our universe, so it is useful", "We can use lots of things with math such as handling money or running a business.", "math is the underlying rule that defines everything."], "subject": "not", "cf_subject": "very", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Please turn on the lights? It is shinny\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Please turn off the lights? It is shinny\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people cannot see well in shinny areas", "Lights are turn on only in the dark places", "One should not turn the lights on when it is shiny."], "subject": "on", "cf_subject": "off", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Racism is over\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Racism is hurtful\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Racism is wrong and unfortunately still around today", "Racism is based upon stereotypes.", "Racism is not an event with the ability to be over."], "subject": "over", "cf_subject": "hurtful", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"people behave softly if they are angry\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"people behave badly if they are angry\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["usually people behave indifferently while in anger", "It is human nature not to behave softly if a human is angry", "People are difficult and harsh to be around when they are angry."], "subject": "softly", "cf_subject": "badly", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"There are beautiful planes here and there in the garden\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"There are beautiful flowers here and there in the garden\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A plane can never be seen in garden", "Planes are not grown in a garden.", "flowers grow in the dirt"], "subject": "planes", "cf_subject": "flowers", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Barbies are the horrible desire for kids\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Barbies are a fantastic desire for kids\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There is nothing wrong with kids desiring dolls as toys", "Barbies are an innocent toy girls usually play with.", "Kids do not desire horrible things and barbies are leable."], "subject": "the horrible", "cf_subject": "a fantastic", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He pulled the water over his head when he got into bed.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He pulled the covers over his head when he got into bed.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people put covers not water on the bed", "Water cannot be pulled over a person's head", "Water on the head at bedtime would cause a person to stay awake."], "subject": "water", "cf_subject": "covers", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she sipped a shoe\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she sipped a coffee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["shoes are inedible", "Shoes are not liquid.", "Do you use a shoe for walking not drinking out of"], "subject": "shoe", "cf_subject": "coffee", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she eats a table for breakfast every day\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she eats an egg for breakfast every day\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["eggs are edible while tables are inedible", "a table is inedible", "Tables are inedible for humans."], "subject": "a table", "cf_subject": "an egg", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He hide a lion in the closet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He hide his shoes in the closet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No owns lions as pets.", "A lion couldn't be hidden in the closet because it is too big", "One cannot hide a lion  in the closet."], "subject": "a lion", "cf_subject": "his shoes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She turned the sun off.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She turned the light off.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Humans cannot control the sun", "People can't turn off the sun", "The sun is in the sky and it has no switch"], "subject": "sun", "cf_subject": "light", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Fish swim in sand.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Fish swim in water.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fish live in water.", "you go swimming in liquid, and sand is a solid.", "Fish can never swim in sand as it cannot survive when taken out of water."], "subject": "sand.", "cf_subject": "water.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put the cat in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put an orange in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["cats can die in a refrigerator for too long", "a cat is a living animal", "He put an orange in the fridge and not cat."], "subject": "the cat", "cf_subject": "an orange", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Jerry has orange serfs with flamingos printed on them.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Jerry has orange undies with flamingos printed on them.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Humans are not orange.", "serfs are people", "a person cannot wear serfs"], "subject": "serfs", "cf_subject": "undies", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"His glasses are clear so he wipes them clean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"His glasses are blurry so he wipes them clean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["clear glasses don't need to be clean anymore", "Clean glasses don't need to be wiped.", "We only wipe things that are dirty"], "subject": "clear", "cf_subject": "blurry", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He rides his apple.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He rides his bike.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An apple is a kind of fruit and can`t be ridden.", "You cannot ride an apple.", "It is impossible to ride an apple."], "subject": "apple.", "cf_subject": "bike.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she drove a pencil\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she drove a car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a pencil is a kind of stationery which cannot be driven", "A pencil is not a vehicle.", "A pencil is not a conveyance."], "subject": "pencil", "cf_subject": "car", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she eats a pillow after her workout\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she eats an orange after her workout\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a pillow is inedible", "Pillows lack caloric content.", "Pillows are inedible"], "subject": "a pillow", "cf_subject": "an orange", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"CNN is for sports\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"CNN covers the news\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["CNN covers the news and ESPN covers sports.", "CNN is a news network.", "CNN is not just for sports, but news as well."], "subject": "is for sports", "cf_subject": "covers the news", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a horse in the cage\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a bird in the cage\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a horse is much bigger than a cage", "A horse is stored near a barn.", "A bird can be put in the cage but a horse cannot."], "subject": "horse", "cf_subject": "bird", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a bear into a pot\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a flower into a pot\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a pot is much smaller than a bear", "A bear is typically too large to fit in a pot.", "A pot is too small to hold a bear."], "subject": "bear", "cf_subject": "flower", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my son has four big hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my son has two big hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one has four hans", "Humans have two hands. Monkeys have four hands.", "If son is a human it have only two hands otherwise it have any defect in its genes"], "subject": "four", "cf_subject": "two", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the cat in the bowl\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the salad in the bowl\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The cat is much bigger than the bowl", "A cat wouldn't fit in a bowl.", "Cats do not fit in bowls."], "subject": "cat", "cf_subject": "salad", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put some money in the oven.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a fish in the oven.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the oven is used to make food but not store money", "You would burn it.", "Money is made from paper and would be destroyed in the oven."], "subject": "some money", "cf_subject": "a fish", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He shucked a fish\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He shucked and oyster\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You can't shuck fish", "fish do not have shells", "fish arent able to be shucked"], "subject": "a fish", "cf_subject": "and oyster", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"We bought a painting from the farmer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"We bought fresh corn from the farmer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A farmer grows crops.", "The farmer sells crops.", "artists sell paintings not farmers"], "subject": "a painting", "cf_subject": "fresh corn", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"all watermelons have seeds\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"all watermelons have water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["some watermelons are seedless", "Not all watermelons have seeds.", "Some watermelons don't have seeds."], "subject": "seeds", "cf_subject": "water", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"every person take stones for breakfast\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"every person take food for breakfast\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["nobody eats stones", "Breakfast consists of food items eaten in the morning, and stones are not food.", "Stones are not food and are not eaten for breakfast."], "subject": "stones", "cf_subject": "food", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he turned the table on\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he turned the light on\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there is no switch on the table", "Tables cannot be \"turned on.\"", "A table is not electrical so can't be turned on."], "subject": "table", "cf_subject": "light", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She erased a campfire with an eraser.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She erased a chalkboard with an eraser.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A campfire would burn an eraser.", "Erasers are used to wipe chalk not real campfires", "Erasers won't erase fires."], "subject": "campfire", "cf_subject": "chalkboard", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she baked a horse at Christmas\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she baked a chicken at Christmas\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there are no traditions to bake a horse at Christmas", "Horse is a animal which can not be baked", "People don't eat horses, especially on Christmas"], "subject": "horse", "cf_subject": "chicken", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I walk without moving\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I walk and moves\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["you move when you're walking", "The act of walking cannot be done without moving", "if I walk logically I have to move, so if I walk I move"], "subject": "without moving", "cf_subject": "and moves", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a stove on the plate.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a soup on the plate.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A stove is much larger than a plate.", "A stove is much larger than a plate. Plates go in stoves.", "A plate is for food to go on, whereas a stove is too large and pointless to put on a plate"], "subject": "stove", "cf_subject": "soup", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"smoking will cherish your health\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"smoking is injurious to health\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["smoking does nothing good for our health", "Cigarettes and other smoking materials contain toxins which damage our bodies.", "Smoking will damage your health."], "subject": "will cherish your", "cf_subject": "is injurious to", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the pharmacy sell pets\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the pharmacy sell medications\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the pharmacy is for medicines", "A pharmacy sells medicine, a pet store sells pets.", "Pharmacy sells pills and medical supplies, not pets."], "subject": "pets", "cf_subject": "medications", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The sky is orange\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The sky is blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The sky won't appear orange", "The sky is made of nitrogen which scatters blue light", "The color of the sky is blue."], "subject": "orange", "cf_subject": "blue", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a gorilla into a box\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put old clothes into a box\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a gorilla is much bigger than a box", "Gorillas are typically too large to fit into a box.", "Gorillas are big wild animals that cannot be put inside a box"], "subject": "a gorilla", "cf_subject": "old clothes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He ties his socks before leaving for his flight\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He ties his shoes before leaving for his flight\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Socks do not need to be tied", "You can't tie your socks", "Socks need not be tied."], "subject": "socks", "cf_subject": "shoes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She shaved her eyes.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She shaved her legs.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Eyes don't have hair.", "There is no hairs to shave on the eyes.", "Only eyelids are shaven, not eyes."], "subject": "eyes.", "cf_subject": "legs.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I have two necks.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I have a neck.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A person only has one neck.", "humans only have one neck", "anatomically we have one neck"], "subject": "two necks.", "cf_subject": "a neck.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a motorcycle on the table.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put the salad on the table.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A motorcycle is much larger than a table.", "A motorcycle would break a table if it was on top of it.", "Motorcycles are kept in the parking area."], "subject": "a motorcycle", "cf_subject": "the salad", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"smoking is good for health\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"smoking is injurious to health\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["cigarettes contain many chemicals that will affect your health", "smoking is spoiling health", "Cigarettes and other materials used for smoking contain dangerous and health threatening ingredients."], "subject": "good for", "cf_subject": "injurious to", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"They grabbed a dinosaur from the drawer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"They grabbed a soda from the drawer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A dinosaur wouldn't fit in a drawer.", "Dinosaurs cannot fit in a drawer.", "A dinosaur is too big for a drawer"], "subject": "dinosaur", "cf_subject": "soda", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Elephants are the smallest land mammals.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Elephants are the largest land mammals.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are many mammals smaller than elephant in land.", "There are no land mammals larger than an elephant", "People are mammals and smaller than elephants."], "subject": "smallest", "cf_subject": "largest", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People get fat during famines.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People get killed in famines.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["If you eat less you lose weight.", "People don't get fat when starving", "People starve during famines so they cannot get fat"], "subject": "fat during", "cf_subject": "killed in", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He parked his train in his house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He parked his bike in his house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A train is too large to be parked in a house", "One can park bike or car in the house and not train.", "trains are halted at railway station"], "subject": "train", "cf_subject": "bike", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The elephant is pink.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The elephant is gray.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["he elephant is gray but not pink.", "pink is not the colour of elephants", "Elephants are commonly birthed as a gray color."], "subject": "pink.", "cf_subject": "gray.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He borrowed a grinder from the library\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He borrowed a book from the library\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A library is containing collections of books", "Books are borrowed from the library and not grinder.", "Libaries do not lend out grinders."], "subject": "grinder", "cf_subject": "book", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put all plates in the washing machine to clean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put all dress in the washing machine to clean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Usually washing machine can clean only clothes, plates are cleaned in the dishwasher", "Washing machines don't clean plates.", "Plates are washed in dishwasher."], "subject": "plates", "cf_subject": "dress", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He wears an umbrella on his head.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He wears a hat on his head.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People don't wear umbrellas on their heads.", "An umbrella is useless on a head compared to a hat.", "Umbrellas have to be held by the handle and could not be worn anywhere."], "subject": "an umbrella", "cf_subject": "a hat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he carried a whale in his car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he carried two people in his car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a whale is much bigger than his car", "A whale is too big for a car.", "Whale is too big to be carried in a car."], "subject": "a whale", "cf_subject": "two people", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Janitors create financial models for their company\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Janitors often clean bathrooms for their company\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Most janitors do not create financial models for their company", "janitors arent involved in finance", "Janitors  cannot create financial models for their company."], "subject": "create financial models", "cf_subject": "often clean bathrooms", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a child into the oven\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a cake into the oven\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["it is dangerous to put kids into the oven", "You don't put children in ovens.", "Putting a child into an oven would kill it, which is frowned upon"], "subject": "child", "cf_subject": "cake", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He buy a planet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He buy a house.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You can't buy a planet even with all the money in the world.", "Currently planets are not for sale and are not purchasable.", "Planets are not for sale."], "subject": "planet.", "cf_subject": "house.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He used the mop to clean the carpet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He used the vacuum to clean the carpet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Carpets cannot be cleaned with mops.", "A mop is wet and would only wet and not clean the carpet.", "The mop will make the carpet wet and soggy."], "subject": "mop", "cf_subject": "vacuum", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"An electrician generates electricity.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"An electrician wires houses.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An electrician uses electricity, but does not create it.", "electricity is not generated by a person", "electricity cannot be generated by a person"], "subject": "generates electricity.", "cf_subject": "wires houses.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he was swimming in Hawaii\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he was flying to Hawaii\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is too dangerous to swim to Hawaii", "you cannot swim in an island", "Swimming to Hawaii from another state or continent would be impossible."], "subject": "swimming in", "cf_subject": "flying to", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a pig in her pocket.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put a lipstick in her pocket.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A pig is much bigger than a pocket.", "Pig is too big to put into the pocket", "Pigs are much bigger than pockets"], "subject": "pig", "cf_subject": "lipstick", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a pony in the lock.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put the key in the lock.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A pony is much larger than a lock.", "Ponies are too big.", "Locks require a key to be used."], "subject": "a pony", "cf_subject": "the key", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He left the cat in the kennel.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He left the dog in the kennel.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A cat can't stay in a kennel because dogs and cats hate each other.", "Kennels are meant for canines", "cats dont go into kennels"], "subject": "cat", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"peoples use a handkerchief for eyes while the bike rides\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"peoples use cooling glass for eyes while the bike rides\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["We can not make rides while people using the handkerchief for their eyes", "Handkerchiefs are not for your eyes.", "people use a handkerchief for eyes to wipe them when they cry, not while on a bike ride."], "subject": "a handkerchief", "cf_subject": "cooling glass", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The bowling ball is swimming in the pond.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The big fish are swimming in the pond.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Bowling balls cannot swim, because they don't have fins.", "A bowling ball would sink in a pond and would not be able to swim.", "Bowling balls will sink in water."], "subject": "bowling ball is", "cf_subject": "big fish are", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She washed the car in the sink.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She washed the dish in the sink.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A car is bigger than a sink.", "A car wouldn't fit in the sink.", "Cars cannot fit in a sink."], "subject": "car", "cf_subject": "dish", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The sky is underground\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The sky is blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The sky is always above the ground", "The sky is up in the air so it would be impossible for it to be underground.", "You look up to see the sky, hence it has to be above ground."], "subject": "underground", "cf_subject": "blue", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Jack lost his giraffe\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Jack lost his wallet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["commons don't have giraffes", "A giraffe is too big to lose.", "Giraffe are not pets. Therefore cannot be lost"], "subject": "giraffe", "cf_subject": "wallet", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a motorcycle in his wallet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a coin in his wallet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A motorcycle is bigger than a wallet", "wallets are too small", "One can put a coin the wallet but not motorcycle."], "subject": "motorcycle", "cf_subject": "coin", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She was interviewed after she got the offer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She was interviewed before she got the offer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The interview comes earlier than the offer", "The interview comes before an offer", "She was interviewed before she got the offer."], "subject": "after", "cf_subject": "before", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"if he is retarded,  he will pass the examination\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"if he is brilliant,  he will pass the examination\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["examination is conducted to screen retards", "A person that is retarded does not have the mental facilities in order to pass exams.", "Intelligence rather than retardation is required to pass the examination."], "subject": "retarded,", "cf_subject": "brilliant,", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She came off walking across the Pacific ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She came off sailing across the Pacific ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It's impossible to walk on the water", "You cannot walk on water.", "Mere mortals have a very hard time walking on water."], "subject": "walking", "cf_subject": "sailing", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she threw the football to the batter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she threw the softball to the batter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there are no batters in football games", "A batter plays softball and it would be impractical to hit a football with a bat", "A football is too big to be hit with a bat."], "subject": "football", "cf_subject": "softball", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"An old car is expensive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A new cars are expensive.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An old car might have a lot of miles so it should be more affordable.", "An old car will depreciate in value.", "Cars depreciate in value with age"], "subject": "An old car is", "cf_subject": "A new cars are", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I want a dirty house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I want a clean house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one wants to live in a dirty house", "A dirty house is prone to disease and insects and rodents.", "A dirty house is unhygienic."], "subject": "dirty", "cf_subject": "clean", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the fire is cold\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the fire is warm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the temperature of the fire is high", "Fire is created by heat friction and therefore cannot be cold.", "Fire is hot and would be called ashes if it's cold"], "subject": "cold", "cf_subject": "warm", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"people often use flowers to remind them of important events\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"people often use alarms to remind them of important events\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Flowers cannot remind people of important events", "Flowers don't live long enough to make effective memoranda.", "People use alarms to to remind them of important events rather than flowers."], "subject": "flowers", "cf_subject": "alarms", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She throws a stove in the hat.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She throws a feather in the hat.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A stove is bigger than a hat.", "stove is too big to fit in a hat", "Stove cannot be thrown in the hat"], "subject": "stove", "cf_subject": "feather", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I put many elevators in the car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I put many suitcases in the car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the car doesn't have as much room for things", "Elevators are large parts of buildings, which cannot fit into a car", "an elevator couldn't fit in a car"], "subject": "elevators", "cf_subject": "suitcases", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The house shoved him\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He shoved the girl\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["He shoved him out of the house", "Houses can't shove.", "House cannot be shoved."], "subject": "The house shoved him", "cf_subject": "He shoved the girl", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she bought two supermarket tickets\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she bought two cinema tickets\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a supermarket doesn't need a ticket to enter", "Supermarkets do not require the purchase of tickets to enter.", "You don't need tickets to go to the supermarket."], "subject": "supermarket", "cf_subject": "cinema", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put an airplane on the bed\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a pillow on the bed\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["an airplane is bigger than a bed", "a plane is too big to put on a bed", "An airplane won't fit on a bed."], "subject": "he an airplane", "cf_subject": "He a pillow", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Pens are for painting\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Pens are for writing\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pens are a writing utensil", "Pens are not brushes.", "A pen is not made for painting."], "subject": "painting", "cf_subject": "writing", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she put a horse in the washing machine\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she put her cloths in the washing machine\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["horse is bigger than washing machine", "A horse is much bigger than a washing machine.", "washing machine is used to wash cloths"], "subject": "a horse", "cf_subject": "her cloths", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he hit a helicopter over the flag\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he hit the ball over the flag\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a helicopter is too heavy to be moved by hitting", "helicopters are too heavy to be hit over a flag", "a helicopter is too heavy to hit"], "subject": "a helicopter", "cf_subject": "the ball", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"it snows in summer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"it snows in winter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["it's too hot to snow in summer", "It usually snows in the winter, not the summer.", "The temperatures n summer are too warm to snow."], "subject": "summer", "cf_subject": "winter", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Stepping through the window is the usual way to enter a room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Stepping through the door is the usual way to enter a room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People nearly always use doors when entering a room.", "Because a window can't be walked through", "Windows are harder to go through"], "subject": "window", "cf_subject": "door", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he bought the bike from the bookstore\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He bought the book from the bookstore\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["bike is generally sold in a bike showroom", "Bookstores sell books, not bikes.", "Books are sold at a bookstore, not bikes"], "subject": "he bike", "cf_subject": "He book", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"honesty should be banned\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"honesty should be encouraged\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["honesty is a good quality which should be encouraged", "Honesty should be encouraged and not banned.", "Honesty is valuable and important"], "subject": "banned", "cf_subject": "encouraged", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Birds were heard barking at night\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Birds were heard singing at night\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Birds don't bark but sing sweetly at night or chirp while dogs bark", "Dogs bark,birds don't.", "birds don't bark"], "subject": "barking", "cf_subject": "singing", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He melted the TV onto the bread.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He melted the cheese onto the bread.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A TV is not a food item.", "You can't melt down a tv to eat", "A TV can onlt be watched not melted on bread"], "subject": "TV", "cf_subject": "cheese", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He inserts his thumb into the car Ignition switch.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He inserts the keys into the car Ignition switch.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The human thumb is larger than the hole of the car Ignition switch.", "The key goes into the ignition switch.", "His thumb will not fit into the car ignition switch."], "subject": "his thumb", "cf_subject": "the keys", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"i use my dog to play cricket\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"i use the bat to play cricket\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one can play the cricket ball by their's dog", "A dog is not the proper equipment to play cricket with", "It would be cruel to use a dog as a cricket bat."], "subject": "my dog", "cf_subject": "the bat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Bats can ride bicycles.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Bats can fly perfectly.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Bats are too small to ride bicycles.", "A bat can not ride a bicycle.", "their legs are not long enough to reach the pedels"], "subject": "ride bicycles.", "cf_subject": "fly perfectly.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"people usually walk backward\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"people usually walk forward\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is dangerous to walk backward on the street for people will hit others", "People don't walk backwards because it is difficult and makes it hard to see what's in front of you", "People usually walk forwards."], "subject": "backward", "cf_subject": "forward", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"donkeys walk on two legs\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"donkeys walk on four legs\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["donkeys have four legs to walk on", "Donkeys walk on four legs because of the way their body is designed", "Donkeys walk on four legs."], "subject": "two", "cf_subject": "four", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He washed the sky\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He washed the dishes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Anyone can wash the sky", "It is impossible to wash the sky.", "It is not possible to wash the sky"], "subject": "sky", "cf_subject": "dishes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He planted a chair in the jar.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He planted a plant in the jar.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A chair is much larger than a jar.", "chair cannot be planted", "A chair is not a plant and wouldn't fit in a jar."], "subject": "chair", "cf_subject": "plant", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I rescued my goldfish from the shelter.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I rescued my dog from the shelter.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are not shelters for goldfish.", "There arent any shelters for goldfishes.", "Shelters do not normally care for goldfish"], "subject": "goldfish", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He takes the house from the washing machine.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She takes the clothes from the washing machine.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The house is bigger than the washing machine.", "A house is far too large to fit in a washing machine", "A House will not fit into a washing machine"], "subject": "He house", "cf_subject": "She clothes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I take the submarine to work every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I take the train to work every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Submarines are not a mode of public transport.", "Submarines are used for underwater travel.", "Submarine is not a public transport system."], "subject": "submarine", "cf_subject": "train", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The outcome of cutting in line is waiting.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The outcome of getting in line is waiting.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You don't have to wait if you cut in line", "cutting a line means you skip the queue", "The outcome of getting in line is waiting  and not cutting."], "subject": "cutting", "cf_subject": "getting", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"people should study less to get a higher grade in exams\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People should study more to get a higher grade in exams\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["extra studying is required to achieve higher grade", "Higher grades usually come with more studying, not less.", "You should study a lot get good grades"], "subject": "people less", "cf_subject": "People more", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"All proteins are enzymes.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"All enzymes are proteins.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Proteins is the larger set of molecules to which enzymes belong as subsets.", "Enzymes are a type of protein.", "Some proteins are not enzymes."], "subject": "proteins enzymes.", "cf_subject": "enzymes proteins.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The fire will cool you if you touch it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The fire will burn you if you touch it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fire is hot and will burn you.", "The fire will burn you if you touch it.", "Fire is hot, therefore it would not cool you."], "subject": "cool", "cf_subject": "burn", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Sunlight grows in plants.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Plants grow in sunlight.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Sunlight does not grow", "Sunlight is a natural phenomena it cannot grow", "Plants do not grow sunlight."], "subject": "Sunlight grows plants.", "cf_subject": "Plants grow sunlight.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"some people ride tigers to work\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"some people ride bikes to work\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one can ride tigers to work", "You would be crazy to try ride a tiger.", "tigers were wild animals so you cannot ride them"], "subject": "tigers", "cf_subject": "bikes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Joe got a parking ticket because he drives too fast.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Joe got a speeding ticket because he drives too fast.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A parking ticket doesn't depend on how fast one drives.", "The police don't give parking tickets for speeding.", "You get parking tickets when you park illegally not for driving too fast."], "subject": "parking", "cf_subject": "speeding", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a truck in the chair.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put the child in the chair.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A truck is too heavy to put on a chair", "A truck is much larger than a chair, so would not fit into one", "the truck breaks the chair"], "subject": "a truck", "cf_subject": "the child", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She brought a microwave to bed.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She brought a book to bed.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["microwaves don't go in beds", "Microwave cannot be brought to bed as it is heavy.", "A microwave is not used in bed"], "subject": "microwave", "cf_subject": "book", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Orange juice is green.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Orange juice is orange.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Orange juice is the same color as oranges which is orange.", "Oranges are orange and make orange juice", "The inside of an Orange is orange so the juice cannot be green."], "subject": "green.", "cf_subject": "orange.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she put a rhino in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she put a pie in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a rhino is much bigger than the fridge", "A rhino can not fit in the fridge", "rhinos will not fit in a fridge"], "subject": "rhino", "cf_subject": "pie", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He took his goldfish for a walk\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He took his dog for a walk\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A goldfish does not have legs", " goldfish cannot walk.", "Goldfish lives in water and cannot walk."], "subject": "goldfish", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Plastic is not reusable\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"plastic can be transparent\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Plastic can be recycled", "Plastic can be reusable.", "Some plastics are reusable because they are transparent."], "subject": "Plastic is not reusable", "cf_subject": "plastic can be transparent", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He returned five octopus to the library\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He returned five books to the library\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["octopus live in the ocean", "Octopus belong in the sea.", "Octopus are returned to the ocean"], "subject": "octopus", "cf_subject": "books", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The chef put extra lemons on the pizza.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The chef put extra mushrooms on the pizza.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Lemons are not a pizza topping.", "lemons would be awful on a pizza", "lemons don't go on pizzas"], "subject": "lemons", "cf_subject": "mushrooms", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The window looks out her\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She looks out the window\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Windows doesn't look at people", "The woman looks out the window.", "The window cannot look as it has not eyes."], "subject": "The window looks out her", "cf_subject": "She looks out the window", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy ate a basketball\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy ate a donut\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You cannot eat a basketball", "the basketball is too big to go in the boy's mouth", "A boy would eat food, a basketball is a ball that you play a sport with."], "subject": "basketball", "cf_subject": "donut", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he wrote a great hamburger\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he wrote a great novel\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["nobody can write a hamburger", "A hamburger is made, not written.", "A hamburger is a food item made to be eaten, not written."], "subject": "hamburger", "cf_subject": "novel", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He purchased chemical and cement to prepare a sandwich for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He purchased breads and vegetables to prepare a sandwich for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one can buy chemical and cement to make a sandwich", "Chemicals and cement dont belong on a sandwich.", "Chemicals and cement are not ingredients in a sandwich."], "subject": "chemical cement", "cf_subject": "breads vegetables", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the family adopted a dinosaur to be their new pet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the family adopted a dog to be their new pet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the dinosaurs died out long ago", "Dinosaurs cannot be adopted because they are extinct", "dinosaurs no longer exist"], "subject": "dinosaur", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the comedian performed magic tricks\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the comedian made some jokes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the comedian isn't usually a magician", "Comedians tell jokes, magic tricks are performed by magicians", "Comedians perform jokes, not magic."], "subject": "performed magic tricks", "cf_subject": "made some jokes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People like to eat land\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People like to eat pizza\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People don't eat earth as food", "People like to eat food.", "Land is not healthy to ingest."], "subject": "land", "cf_subject": "pizza", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I would like to fry a laptop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I would like to buy a laptop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["frying the laptop will damage the machine", "Would be illogical to fry a laptop", "You can't fry a laptop."], "subject": "fry", "cf_subject": "buy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The goldfish ate a cat.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cat ate a goldfish.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Goldfish are herbivores", "A cat is bigger than a goldfish.", "Fishes don't feed on animals on land"], "subject": "goldfish cat.", "cf_subject": "cat goldfish.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The worm swallowed the bird.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The bird swallowed the worm.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the bird is much larger while the worm is much smaller.", "worms cant swallow a whole bird", "A worm is too small to swallow a bird."], "subject": "worm bird.", "cf_subject": "bird worm.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The park ran to him\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He ran to the park\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A park cannot move", "parks do not move", "parks dont run to people"], "subject": "The park ran to him", "cf_subject": "He ran to the park", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Snowmen are made of sand.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Snowmen are made of snow.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Snowmen get their name from what they are made of.", "Snowman are made of snow.", "Sand is at the beach"], "subject": "sand.", "cf_subject": "snow.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I enter in a bottle\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I enter in a car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a bottle is smaller than a person", "A person wouldn't fit in a bottle.", "Under normal conditions, a bottle will not be large enough for a person to enter."], "subject": "bottle", "cf_subject": "car", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The girl broke her lamp while ice skating.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The girl broke her arm while ice skating.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You do not bring a lamp with you while ice skating.", "The girl would not hold a lamp while ice skating.", "You wouldn't take a lamp ice skating."], "subject": "lamp", "cf_subject": "arm", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Lobsters live in the mountains\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Lobsters live in the ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Lobsters needs water to live", "Lobsters live in the sea.", "Lobsters live in the sea, not the mountains"], "subject": "mountains", "cf_subject": "ocean", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"That morning, Kate had dinner and left for work\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"That morning, Kate had breakfast and left for work\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["dinner is the meal that one takes in the evening rather than in the morning", "Dinner is eaten in the evening.", "dinner time is night"], "subject": "dinner", "cf_subject": "breakfast", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A COW EAT A MOUNTAIN\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A COW EAT A GRASS\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["COW CANNOT EAT A MOUNTAIN", "mountains cannot be eaten", "Cows can't eat a whole a mountain; they are huge and mostly inedible rock."], "subject": "MOUNTAIN", "cf_subject": "GRASS", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My sister is a male\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My sister is a female\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a sister means a girl, which means female", "sister means female", "sister is a feminine word"], "subject": "male", "cf_subject": "female", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the fish live in computers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The fish live in rivers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Computers don't have water for the fish.", "Fish live in water.", "Fish must live in water to survive, there is no water for a fish to live in inside a computer"], "subject": "the computers.", "cf_subject": "The rivers.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People may consider you polite if you do not say please when asking for something.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People may consider you rude if you do not say please when asking for something.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["asking for something without saying please is a rude behavior", "not talking please is impolite", "Please is polite."], "subject": "polite", "cf_subject": "rude", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the dog growled, then taught the boy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the dog growled, then charged the boy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the dog doesn't have the ability to teach people", "a dog cant teach", "the dog growled bite the boy"], "subject": "taught", "cf_subject": "charged", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The protein bar ate me\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I ate a protein bar\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The protein bar is a kind of food", "One can eat a protein bar but a protein bar cannot eat a person.", "people eat protein bars"], "subject": "The protein bar ate me", "cf_subject": "I ate a protein bar", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My heater cools a lot\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My heater gets very hot\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A heater is for heating, so it does not cool", "Heaters don't make things cool.", "A heater is not able to cool"], "subject": "cools a lot", "cf_subject": "gets very hot", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"dolphins are fast to fly\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"dolphins are fast to swim\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["dolphins live in the sea", "Dolphins live in the ocean and do not have wings.", "Dolphins are incapable of flying."], "subject": "fly", "cf_subject": "swim", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Swimming is a common winter activity\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Swimming is a common summer activity\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Most people do not swim during the winter", "It is too cold outside for most people to swim in winter.", "The water is too cold in winter."], "subject": "winter", "cf_subject": "summer", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the man took his door to the dry cleaner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the man took his suit to the dry cleaner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the dry cleaner doesn't receive anything other than clothes", "dry cleaner we put dresses", "Dry cleaners clean clothes not doors."], "subject": "door", "cf_subject": "suit", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the cow eats the bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the cow eats the grass\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["bikes are inedible for cows", "A bike is not eatable by cow", "A cow is an able to chew a bike"], "subject": "bike", "cf_subject": "grass", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Cars stop at a green light.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Cars stop at a red light.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A green light means to pass", "Green lights mean \"go\", not \"stop\"", "Cars stop at a red light."], "subject": "green", "cf_subject": "red", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the Internet will disperse people\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Internet helps people stay connected\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Internet equip distant people to make the communication easily", "The internet has connections and satellites all over the world that helps people stay connected worldwide.", "The internet brings people together by making the world connected with technology."], "subject": "the Internet will disperse people", "cf_subject": "Internet helps people stay connected", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother waters his phone every morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother waters his flowers every morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["watering a phone may damage it", "you don't water a phone, you water plants.", "Water destroys the circuit board of a phone and makes the phone malfunction."], "subject": "phone", "cf_subject": "flowers", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A cat eats a building\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A cat eats a fish\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A building is made of bricks and can not eat buy cats", "Cats are too small to eat buildings.", "cat is a small animal . it's mouth is also small like him/her"], "subject": "building", "cf_subject": "fish", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"grass grows in the water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"grass grows on the ground\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["grass needs to grow on the ground to absorb nutrition from the soil", "grass grows from the earth", "grass need soil for grow"], "subject": "in water", "cf_subject": "on ground", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she cooked mosquitos and ants for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she cooked pasta and sushi for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["few people eat mosquitos and ants", "Most people do not eat mosquito and ants for a meal.", "Mosquitoes and ants are not considered edible food sources, and would therefore not make a good dinner."], "subject": "mosquitos ants", "cf_subject": "pasta sushi", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You can sell a baby on Facebook\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You can sell unwanted items on Facebook\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Selling babies is illegal everywhere", "You can not sell a human being.", "Selling a baby is illegal and immoral."], "subject": "a baby", "cf_subject": "unwanted items", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You can send the book by email\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You can send the photos by email\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You cannot send a book by email", "You can't send a physical book threw email unless you copy all of the pages onto your computer.", "A physical book would need to be sent by regular mail, it cannot be transmitted via electronic mail."], "subject": "book", "cf_subject": "photos", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Tacos was Johnny's favorite drink\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Tacos was Johnny's favorite food\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["tacos are food not drink", "Tacos are a food that you eat not drink", " it went from a solid substance to a liquid substance."], "subject": "drink", "cf_subject": "food", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The snake ate the elephant.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The snake ate the bird.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The elephant is much bigger than the snake", "An elephant is too big for a snake to eat.", "Elephants are to large for a snake to eat."], "subject": "elephant.", "cf_subject": "bird.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Walking is faster than driving\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Running is faster than walking\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The speed of walking is about 3km/h while driving is 60km/h", "Walking would not make sense to be fast. When walking someone is moving slowly.", "It's impossible for someone to walk as fast as a car would drive."], "subject": "Walking driving", "cf_subject": "Running walking", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I saw my friend's car dancing\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I saw my friend's cat dancing\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A car is inanimate and it can not dance", "Cars are not able to dance.", "Cars don't move in their own, and don't have the ability to move to music, so they can't dance."], "subject": "car", "cf_subject": "cat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He picked up his piano and played a chord\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He picked up his guitar and played a chord\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pianos are heavy and can't easily be picked up", "A piano plays notes, not chords.", "Piano dosent have chords."], "subject": "piano", "cf_subject": "guitar", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Mary won the race tomorrow\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Mary won the race yesterday\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Tomorrow in the future and we can not know what will happen", "Mary  can't know the outcome of what happens tomorrow.", "You can't win something that hasn't happened yet"], "subject": "tomorrow", "cf_subject": "yesterday", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the clothes are running away\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the clothes are being washed\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["clothes can do nothing itself", "Clothes do not have legs and feet to run.", "Clothes are inanimate objects and cannot run"], "subject": "running away", "cf_subject": "being washed", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my mother cooked the stone\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my mother cooked the chicken\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people can't eat stone", "A stone cannot be cooked.", "A stone is not an item that requires cooking, nor is it a food"], "subject": "stone", "cf_subject": "chicken", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You can use a Hospital to sleep while away from home\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You can use a hotel to sleep while away from home\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a Hospital is for sick people", "Hospital where the place whre the patients used to visit the doctor. We are  going to hospital to treat our health problems", "You can use hotel to sleep while a way from home."], "subject": "Hospital", "cf_subject": "hotel", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He waited for his flight at the bus stop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He waited for his bus at the bus stop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is impossible to board a flight from the bus stop", "Flights are commonly land on the airport", "Airplanes cannot land at bus station"], "subject": "flight", "cf_subject": "bus", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Carol turned on the potato\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Carol turned on the flashlight\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A potato can't be turned on", "Potatoes have no turn on switch.", "A potato is not powered."], "subject": "potato", "cf_subject": "flashlight", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he purchased lime and cement to prepare sandwiches for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he purchased bread and vegetables to prepare sandwiches for dinner\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["lime and cement has some inedible chemicals", "People do not eat lime and cement", "Lime and cement are not used to make sandwhiches"], "subject": "lime cement", "cf_subject": "bread vegetables", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"shirts are clothes that birds wear\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"shirts are clothes that people wear\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["birds don't need clothes", "Birds do not wear clothes", "Birds wear no clothes."], "subject": "birds", "cf_subject": "people", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The sun is very cold.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The sun is very hot.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The average temperature of the sun of 5.778 K can be considered hot.", "The sun is made of fire and can not be very cold.", "Without the sun, the earth will freeze and there will be no life on earth."], "subject": "cold.", "cf_subject": "hot.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the ripe apples taste spicy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the ripe apples taste sweet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["apples have no spicy ingredients", "green apples are spicy, ripe apples are sweet", "Apples taste sweet not spicy."], "subject": "spicy", "cf_subject": "sweet", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The black owl is red\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The black owl is large\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["If the owl is black then it cannot be read", "The owl is black so how can it be red.", "Black and red are completely different colors."], "subject": "red", "cf_subject": "large", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman dyes her feet every six weeks at the salon.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman dyes her hair every six weeks at the salon.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Women don't dye their feet.", "Because the salon don't dye feet.", "Salons are meant for hair and feet, especially female feet, do not have hair so they have no place being dyed at a salon."], "subject": "feet", "cf_subject": "hair", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Houses are found in lakes.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Tim painted his house yesterday.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Houses are places that people live in and people don't live in lakes.", "A house would be full of water if in a lake", "Houses are found on dry land."], "subject": "Houses are found in lakes.", "cf_subject": "Tim painted his house yesterday.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"crackhead does not take drugs\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"crackhead is a drug addict\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["crackhead is a term for drug addicts", "If you are a crackhead, you take drugs.", "drugs are addictive to people"], "subject": "does not take drugs", "cf_subject": "is a drug addict", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Asia is part of Dubai\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Dubai is located in Asia\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dubai is a city, but Asia is a continent.", "An entire continent can not be part of a city.", "Asia is a continent so it is bigger than Dubai"], "subject": "Asia part of Dubai", "cf_subject": "Dubai located in Asia", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The teachers scolded the principal.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The principal scolded the teachers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The teacher can't able to scold the principal.", "The principal is in charge of the teachers.", "employees do not have the right to discipline their employer"], "subject": "teachers principal.", "cf_subject": "principal teachers.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put on a bike.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put on a shirt.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The bike is not cloth for people to put on", "bikes are not clothing to put on, shirts and pants are.", "A bike can't be worn."], "subject": "bike.", "cf_subject": "shirt.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the baby held a grizzly bear\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the baby held the teddy bear\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a baby would be eaten by a grizzly bear", "Baby can hold a teddy bear but not grizzly bear.", "A grizzly bear is bigger than a baby and would eat a baby."], "subject": "a grizzly", "cf_subject": "the teddy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"TORTOISE RUNS FASTER THAN CAT\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"CAT RUNS FASTER THAN TORTOISE\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Tortoise runs very slow, but cats run very fast", "Tortoises move very slowly.", "Tortoise are one of the slowest animals."], "subject": "TORTOISE CAT", "cf_subject": "CAT TORTOISE", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he went up a valley\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he went up the hill\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["valley is a depression", "A valley is downhill.", "Valleys are low areas so you can't go up them."], "subject": "a valley", "cf_subject": "the hill", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My neighbor is a fish.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Fish live in the ocean.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["My neighbor is human", "Fish live in the ocean", "A fish cannot own a house."], "subject": "My neighbor is a fish.", "cf_subject": "Fish live in the ocean.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a turkey is a pig\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a turkey is a bird\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pigs and turkeys are different animals", "Turkeys are an entirely different species than pigs.", "A turkey and a pig are two different animals and species."], "subject": "pig", "cf_subject": "bird", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The farm is in carpet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The farm is in Kansas\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A carpet is smaller than the farm", "Carpet is not where a farm can be.", "A carpet is a flat piece of fabric."], "subject": "carpet", "cf_subject": "Kansas", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy kicked the house.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy kicked the ball.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A house is too heavy for a human to kick it off", "There is no practical reason to kick a house", "The boy would have a sore foot if he kicked the house."], "subject": "house.", "cf_subject": "ball.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a shark into the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put the chicken on the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A shark is much bigger than the fridge.", "Sharks are too big.", "Fridge cannot accommodate a shark."], "subject": "a shark into", "cf_subject": "the chicken on", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The kid took her mother to the school\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The mother took her kid to the school\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Parents are who take their kids to school", "practically a kid won't be allowed to lead a mother to the school.", "Kids don't take parents to school."], "subject": "kid mother", "cf_subject": "mother kid", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The lizard climbed the ocean.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The lizard climbed a rock.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The lizards live on the land.", "you cant climb an ocean", "Lizards will drown in the ocean"], "subject": "the ocean.", "cf_subject": "a rock.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I was doing my laundry at the library.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I was reading a book at the library.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no washers and dryers at the library.", "the library does have have a washer and dryer", "libraries do not have laundry facilities in them."], "subject": "doing my laundry", "cf_subject": "reading a book", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother always takes mud in the morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother always has breakfast in the morning\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["nobody takes mud in the morning", "You cannot take mud.", "People don't eat mud."], "subject": "takes mud", "cf_subject": "has breakfast", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A dog can cut down a tree.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A dog can pee on a tree.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A dog can not use an ax", "A dog is not big enough to cut down a tree.", "The dog has no hands so he can use a saw."], "subject": "cut down", "cf_subject": "pee on", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the teacher was harvesting wheat in the classroom\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The teacher was teaching English in the classroom\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Classrooms don't have cultivated fields in them", "Harvesting wheat requires farmland, and farmland is not in a classroom.", "Wheat is harvested from fields not classrooms."], "subject": "the harvesting wheat", "cf_subject": "The teaching English", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"HE WAS GOING TO RESTAURANT AFTER ACCIDENT\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"HE WAS GOING TO HOSPITAL AFTER ACCIDENT\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A RESTAURANT DOES NOT HAVE DOCTORS OR MEDICAL EQUIPMENTS", "Restaurant don't provide medical services.", "if you are hurt then you need to go to a hospital for treament after an accident"], "subject": "RESTAURANT", "cf_subject": "HOSPITAL", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My glasses help me smell\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My glasses help me see\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Glasses are only used for aiding vision", "Glasses are made from curved glass to help focus light only.", "Nose help to smell and glass is use for drinks"], "subject": "smell", "cf_subject": "see", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People use cars to fly.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People use cars for transportation.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cars can't fly.", "Cars are used for driving on terrain.", "Car is not a flying object, it runs on the road."], "subject": "to fly.", "cf_subject": "for transportation.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The cow ate the chickens in the pasture.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cow ate the grass in the pasture.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cows do not eat meat.", "cows are not carnivorous", "Cows eat grass not meat."], "subject": "chickens", "cf_subject": "grass", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Fruits and vegetables provide toxins\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Fruits and vegetables provide nutrients\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fruits and vegetables provide nutrients instead of toxins", "fruits and vegetables are nutritious and provide nutrients that are healthy for you.", "Fruits and vegetables provide nutrients"], "subject": "toxins", "cf_subject": "nutrients", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Water tastes like orange juice\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"orange juice tastes like orange\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["water is tasteless", "This does not make sense because water has a different flavor than orange juice.", "Water can't taste like something it isn't."], "subject": "Water tastes like orange juice", "cf_subject": "orange juice tastes like orange", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The frog ate a tiger\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The tiger ate a frog\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Frog is much smaller than a tiger", "Tiger can eat a frog and the frog cannot eat a tiger.", "Frogs are much too small to eat a tiger and frogs only eat bugs."], "subject": "frog tiger", "cf_subject": "tiger frog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he learned with his refrigerator before the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he learned with his textbooks before the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["refrigerator doesn't have any information for the exam", "You learn from a book.", "Refrigerators have no capacity to teach about exams."], "subject": "refrigerator", "cf_subject": "textbooks", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She checked the bucket for the time\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She turned around to check the time\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There is no time in the bucket", "A bucket is used to put things in.", "Buckets don't tell time."], "subject": "checked the bucket for", "cf_subject": "turned around to check", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"After sunset sky turns blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"After sunset sky turns dark\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Sky becomes dark after sunset", "The blue tint is because of sunlight reflecting off of moisture and dust in the air.", "The sky turns almost black after sunset"], "subject": "blue", "cf_subject": "dark", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The Carpenter Chopped the Train\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The carpenter Chopped the Woods\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the train is too hard to chop", "A carpenter cuts wood.", "It would be hard for a carpenter to chop a train as trains are made of metal."], "subject": "Carpenter Train", "cf_subject": "carpenter Woods", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Sally taught her students burglary\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Sally taught her students English\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Burglary is illegal", "You can't teach students burglary in a school legally.", "Burglary is not a subject to be taught."], "subject": "burglary", "cf_subject": "English", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A liquid becomes a solid when it reaches boiling point\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A liquid becomes a gas when it reaches boiling point\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A liquid becomes a solid below its melting point", "liquids become solid when they cool down", "A  liquid cannot become  a solid when it reaches boiling point."], "subject": "solid", "cf_subject": "gas", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The supermarket only sells cars\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I shop at the supermarket\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["They have a variety of goods and services in the supermarket, mainly household supplies", "A supermarket implies the sale of smaller goods like groceries or toiletries.", "Supermarkets don't sell cars."], "subject": "The supermarket only sells cars", "cf_subject": "I shop at the supermarket", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The man ate the bowl when he was hungry.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man ate the salad when he was hungry.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People cannot eat bowls.", "The bowl is not edible.", "One cannot eat a bowl"], "subject": "bowl", "cf_subject": "salad", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the mouse ate the cat\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the cat ate the mouse\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a cat is a carnivore that eats mice", "A mouse is too small to eat a cat.", "The cat is too big for a mouse to eat."], "subject": "mouse cat", "cf_subject": "cat mouse", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My brother adopter a tiger from a shelter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My brother adopted a cat from a shelter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A tiger is a dangerous animal, he belongs in the wild", "Tigers cannot be adopted from shelters.", "Tiger's are not adopted out by shelters."], "subject": "adopter tiger", "cf_subject": "adopted cat", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I would like to fry a PS4\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I would like to buy a PS4\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A PS4 is a game console and putting it on a frying pan would damage the machine", "Electronic objects, such as a PS4, cannot be fried like food.", "You can't cook a ps4."], "subject": "fry", "cf_subject": "buy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the fan was blowing guns\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the fan was blowing air\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["guns are too heavy for fans to blow", "A fan blows wind, not guns.", "a fan doesn't have  guns"], "subject": "guns", "cf_subject": "air", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Boats float on the road\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Boats float on the river\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Boats need water to float", "Boats are designed to float and move through water, not dry ground.", "Boats float in water not the road."], "subject": "road", "cf_subject": "river", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Sally taught mathematics for ninety years since she was 30\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Sally taught mathematics for nine years since she was 30\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["it is impossible for a person to work for ninety years from the age of 30", "30 plus ninety is one hunderd and twenty, Sally cannot be so old", "In order for Sally to teach for 90 years, she must be at least 90 years old"], "subject": "ninety", "cf_subject": "nine", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He jumped through the happiness\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He jumped through the window\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["happiness is kind of feeling", "You cannot jump through a state of mind.", "You can't jump through an emotion."], "subject": "happiness", "cf_subject": "window", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Each day someone gets younger.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Each day someone gets older.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["As time progresses people always get older.", "People can only get older.", "Each day increases age."], "subject": "younger.", "cf_subject": "older.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he drove to the moon before it closed at 9pm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he drove to the store before it closed at 9pm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the moon is too far away from us", "Moon doesn't have a closing time.", "The moon is open all night, and most of the day."], "subject": "moon", "cf_subject": "store", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"elephants eat rabbits and rats\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"elephants eat grass and leaves\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the elephant is a herbivore and does not eat animals", "Elephants are herbivores.", "elephants are herbivores"], "subject": "rabbits rats", "cf_subject": "grass leaves", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Joey likes to eat poison\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Joey likes to eat fruits\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["If you eat poison, you will die", "Joey would be dead if he actually ate poison", "Joey would die or get very ill if he ate poison."], "subject": "poison", "cf_subject": "fruits", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"There are four years each season.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"There are four seasons each year.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a year can be dived into four seasons", "A year is bigger than a season, so a Year includes four seasons.", "There are four seasons in each year and not four years each season."], "subject": "years season.", "cf_subject": "seasons year.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Plastic is more expensive than gold.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Gold is more expensive than plastic.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Gold is a precious metal while plastic is cheap", "Gold costs more per ounce than plastic.", "How expensive something is depends on the supply of it and the demand for it, and gold is far rarer and in more demand than plastic, so it costs more, not less."], "subject": "Plastic gold.", "cf_subject": "Gold plastic.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"They stored food in the ground in summer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"They stored food in the fridge in summer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Food should be stored in low temperature", "As summers are hot food will be spoilt if kept in normal temperature.", "It would not be a good idea to store food in the ground at any time as it could rot and make you sick."], "subject": "ground", "cf_subject": "fridge", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Something you find at the road is a t.v.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Something you find at a home is a t.v.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one watches t.v. on road.", "There is no place to plug in a TV on a road.", "TVs are not the most common item you would find on a road"], "subject": "the road", "cf_subject": "a home", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"onions are grown in the tree\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"onions are grown under the ground\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["onions are not possible to grow in the tree", "Onions don't grow on trees.", "Fruits grow on trees."], "subject": "in tree", "cf_subject": "under ground", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You should leave the lights on when you leave the room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You should turn the lights off when you leave the room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Leaving the lights on is a waste of electricity", "Leaving the lights on waste energy", "Leaving the lights on will make the light bulb have a shorter life."], "subject": "leave on", "cf_subject": "turn off", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A train is used for sailing\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A train is used for traveling\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Trains travel on rails", "A train is a land based vehicle and sailing is an activity done on water.", "A train is used for travelling and not sailing."], "subject": "sailing", "cf_subject": "traveling", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A soldier shot with a guitar.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A soldier fired with a revolver.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A guitar serves to make musical sounds.", "No shots can be fired using a guitar", "guitar is a musical instrument soldier cannot be shot with it."], "subject": "shot guitar.", "cf_subject": "fired revolver.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Breakfast is eating during the night.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Breakfast is eaten in the morning.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Breakfast is the first meal of the day.", "Breakfast is a morning meal.", "Breakfast is a morning meal."], "subject": "eating during night.", "cf_subject": "eaten in morning.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He went to a petrol station to write the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He went to the examination hall to write the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Exams are conducted in the examination hall,  rather than the petrol station", "petrol stations don't have desks and chairs", "Petrol stations are for fueling up vehicles."], "subject": "a petrol station", "cf_subject": "the examination hall", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"her favorite organ is the telephone\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"her favorite organ is the kidney\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a telephone is made up of electronic components and an organ is made up of cells", "It doesn't make sense a phone is not an organ but an object", "A telephone is not an organ"], "subject": "telephone", "cf_subject": "kidney", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the TV program entertains the fish\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the TV program entertains many people\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["fish don't understand TV programs", "A tv program is not going to entertain fish because they dont understand it", "fish don't understand tv programs"], "subject": "the fish", "cf_subject": "many people", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"It is good to drink saltwater at night\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"It is good to drink milk at night\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Saltwater at night is bad for health", "Saltwater is not healty to drink at night", "saltwater wil make you sick if you drink it"], "subject": "saltwater", "cf_subject": "milk", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Children go to school to laugh\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Children go to school to learn\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Schools prioritize education over entertainment", "Schools are traditionally humorless.", "Learning is serious not a laughing matter"], "subject": "laugh", "cf_subject": "learn", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The wind pushes the tree upright\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The wind blows over a tree\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The wind cannot push a tree to stand up", "Winds are rarely helpful to trees.", "When wind comes, trees sway and cannot stand upright"], "subject": "pushes the tree upright", "cf_subject": "blows over a tree", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A stop sign is always white\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A stop sign is always red\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["white cannot catch the human eye easily", "Stops signs are red to show the danger of not following the instruction", "A stop sign is always red."], "subject": "white", "cf_subject": "red", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"detergents are used in an investigation\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"detergents are used to clean clothes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["investigation can never be done using detergents", "Investigations are based on procedures made with thoughts, not detergents.", "Using detergents wouldn't aid an investigation ."], "subject": "in an investigation", "cf_subject": "to clean clothes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the snake runs on his feet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the snake crawls on his body\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["snakes have no feet to run and can only crawl", "snakes cannot run", "Snakes slitter because they have undeveloped legs/feet."], "subject": "runs feet", "cf_subject": "crawls body", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I play games on my shoes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I play games on my phone\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no games on shoes", "shoes are not for playing games, but wearing", "Shoes is to wear to play game not to play on it"], "subject": "shoes", "cf_subject": "phone", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I hide successfully behind a book\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I hide successfully behind a tree\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People is usually much. Larger than a book", "A human is larger than a book and so could not successfully hide behind one", "A person is too big to hide behind a book."], "subject": "book", "cf_subject": "tree", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The dog yelled at the man.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man yelled at the dog.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the dog only can bark at a man.", "Dogs are not physically made to yell, only bark.", "Dogs only bark."], "subject": "dog man.", "cf_subject": "man dog.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my sister went to the desert to fetch water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my sister went to the pond to fetch water\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the desert is arid and there is little water", "There is no water in the desert.", "one cannot fetch water from desert."], "subject": "desert", "cf_subject": "pond", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Film making can be a single job in the summer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Film making can be a stressful job in the summer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Sinnicle does describe or compare to being stressful", "Film making requires a lot of time.", "Filmmaking is not a single job."], "subject": "single", "cf_subject": "stressful", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Watching sports is fun for all people\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Watching sports is fun to some people\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Some people don't like watching sports", "Watching sports isn't fun for all people because I hate watching sports.", "Watching sports cannot be fun for all people."], "subject": "for all", "cf_subject": "to some", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"An airplane swims in the water.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"An airplane flies through the air.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An airplane is designed to fly in the air.", "Airplanes are either on the ground or in the air and they do not swim, they fly.", "an airplane will break in water"], "subject": "swims in water.", "cf_subject": "flies through air.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He put a dinosaur into the pool\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He put some water into a pool\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a dinosaur is extinct", "Dinosaurs do not exist", "Dinasaurs are very much extinct."], "subject": "a dinosaur the", "cf_subject": "some water a", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a piece of plastic on the bread\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a piece of cheese on the bread\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the plastic usually is toxic", "You can't eat plastic.", "People do not eat plastic because it's not a food"], "subject": "plastic", "cf_subject": "cheese", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Puja almost works 25 to 30 hours every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Puja almost works 12 to 15 hours every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Each day has only 24 hours.", "There are only 24 hours in a single day.", "A day have 24 hours only"], "subject": "25 30", "cf_subject": "12 15", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You should iron your clothes before you wash them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You should iron your clothes after you wash them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Washing the clothes would wrinkle the clothes again", "Clothes have no need to be wrinkle free before they go into the washing machine", "It would be pointless to iron your clothes before you wash them."], "subject": "before", "cf_subject": "after", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the farmers live on a cloud\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the farmers live on a farm\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one lives in the air", "Living on a cloud is impossible because its just water vapor floating in our atmosphere", "You can't live on clouds."], "subject": "cloud", "cf_subject": "farm", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the man put on his airplane\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the man put on his pants\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a person cannot wear an airplane", "An airplane is not clothing", "Airplanes are not clothing"], "subject": "airplane", "cf_subject": "pants", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Put the baby in the driver seat.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Put the baby in the car seat.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Putting the baby in the driver seat is dangerous.", "Baby should be kept in the car seat and not driver seat.", "Drivers should sit in the driver seat and babies are not able to drive"], "subject": "driver", "cf_subject": "car", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The ant stepped on the child, which killed it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The child stepped on the ant, which killed it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An ant is small and cannot step on a child.", "ants arent large enough", "The child can step on the ant and the ant cannot step on the child."], "subject": "ant child,", "cf_subject": "child ant,", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Women are usually larger than men.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Men are usually larger than women.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Women are generally smaller than men.", "Women are actually smaller usually, men have more muscle mass and more ability to gain muscle.", "statistically men are bigger than women due to our biology"], "subject": "Women men.", "cf_subject": "Men women.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She went to the museum next weekend.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She went to the museum last weekend.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You can't do something that hasn't happened yet.", "next weekend did not happen yet.", "Its a coming weekend not next weekend"], "subject": "next", "cf_subject": "last", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I was on date with lion yesterday.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I had dinner with my friends yesterday.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Lion is a fierce animal and he can eat me.", "Lions rarely make good dinner companionship.", "Lions are dangerous creatures."], "subject": "was on date with lion", "cf_subject": "had dinner with my friends", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My mom always cuts my fish's hair.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My mom always cuts my sister's hair.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fish don't have any hair.", "Fish have scales instead of hair like we have", "Fish don't have hair."], "subject": "fish's", "cf_subject": "sister's", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My bird is about forty feet tall.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My bird is about a foot tall.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No bird is 40 feet tall.", "Birds cannot be forty feet tall.", "World's largest bird size is 24 feet"], "subject": "forty feet", "cf_subject": "a foot", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The counter fell off the lamp\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The lamp fell off the counter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The counter is too big and fixed in place", "The lamp sits on a surface, the counter.", "Counters don't sit on lamps."], "subject": "counter lamp", "cf_subject": "lamp counter", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He can cook a whole elephant in a frying pan\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He can cook a whole chicken in a frying pan\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the Whole Elephant is bigger than a pan", "Elephant is much bigger than frying pan.", "an elephant is much bigger than a frying pan"], "subject": "elephant", "cf_subject": "chicken", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he likes to drink motor oil\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he likes to drink cold coffee\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["he will die if he drinks motor oil", "Motor oil is poisonous and can only be used in automobiles.", "motor oil will make you sick"], "subject": "motor oil", "cf_subject": "cold coffee", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Most people sleep in a shoe.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Most people sleep in a bed.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A human is larger than a shoe.", "A person can not fit in a shoe", "shoes are not big enough"], "subject": "shoe.", "cf_subject": "bed.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He flew the airplane to Jupiter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He flew the airplane to Europe\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Airplanes cannot fly in space", "airplanes cannot leave our atmosphere", "Jupiter is in space you would need a space rocket"], "subject": "Jupiter", "cf_subject": "Europe", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She was drinking from a plate\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She was drinking from a cup\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a plate is flat", "Plates are used for food not drinks", "SHE IS DRINKING FROM A CUP"], "subject": "plate", "cf_subject": "cup", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Colgate is a brand of beer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Colgate is a brand of toothpaste\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Colgate is a popular brand of oral hygiene products,  not beer", "Colgate is not something you drink.", "Toothpaste and beer are different classes of item."], "subject": "beer", "cf_subject": "toothpaste", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"If you do your job badly, you will get paid regardless\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"If you do your job well, you will get paid regardless\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Getting paid requires doing a good job", "People who do their job poorly will be fired.", "You do not get paid to do your job badly, you only get paid to do your job well."], "subject": "badly,", "cf_subject": "well,", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother speaks to the house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my brother today speak to me\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["house cannot have ear", "My brother speaks to his friend.", "house is the best friend of my brother"], "subject": "speaks to the house", "cf_subject": "today speak to me", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She strictly does not allow food into her house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She strictly does not allow alcohol into her house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one can bar food into their house as everyone needs to eat", "She strictly does not allow alcohol into her house", "Food is a daily necessity that should be readily available."], "subject": "food", "cf_subject": "alcohol", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Many cancer patients lose their hand because of chemotherapy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Many cancer patients lose their hair because of chemotherapy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cancer patients never lose hands due to chemotherapy", "Chemotherapy treatment does not affect the body in any way that would cause loss of a limb.", "Cancer patients usually lose hair from chemotherapy, not their hands."], "subject": "hand", "cf_subject": "hair", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The whale swam in the sky\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The whale swam in the ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Whales do not swim in the sky", "To swim requires water.", "There is no water in the sky for swimming"], "subject": "sky", "cf_subject": "ocean", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the turtle swam on the land\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The turtle swam in the ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there is no water on land", "Swimming is something that can only be done in water or liquid.", "One cannot swim on land, you need water to swim."], "subject": "the on land", "cf_subject": "The in ocean", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he made dinner on the television\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he made dinner on the stove\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["television is for watching programs", "A television does not have any place for cooking and does not produce enough heat for anyone to cook upon.", "He made dinner on the stove"], "subject": "television", "cf_subject": "stove", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"every people sit quietly on a bus\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Most people sit quietly on the bus\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["some people are talking on a bus", "Most people sit quietly on the bus and not every people.", "the bus is usually noisey"], "subject": "every a", "cf_subject": "Most the", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"ham is made from a cat\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"ham is made from a pig\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["ham meat cut from the thigh of a hog", "Ham is made from a pig and not cat.", "Ham is made from a pig."], "subject": "cat", "cf_subject": "pig", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"One morning I shot an elephant in my pajamas\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"One morning I shot a fly in my pajamas\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An elephant is much bigger to occupy in pajamas", "elephant lives in jungle it cannot enter pajamas", "An elephant is too big to fir inside a person's pajamas."], "subject": "an elephant", "cf_subject": "a fly", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A couple sat on the water to watch the sunset.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A couple sat on a rock to watch the sunset.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one can sit on the water.", "You cannot sit on the water", "you cannot sit on water, only in."], "subject": "the water", "cf_subject": "a rock", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a whale in the car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a woman in his car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A whale is much bigger than the car", "A whale would not fit in the car.", "the whale doesn't fit in a car"], "subject": "whale the", "cf_subject": "woman his", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Eagles are a type of fish\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Eagles are a kind of bird\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["An eagle is a fly animal, a bird", "Eagles cannot live in water like fish", "Eagles eat fish, and are not known for cannibalism."], "subject": "type fish", "cf_subject": "kind bird", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I play catch with a boat\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I play catch with a baseball\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The boat is too large to throw", "A boat is too large to physically be able to play catch with.", "A boat is so big"], "subject": "boat", "cf_subject": "baseball", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he was dancing on the lake\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he was dancing on the floor\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one can float on water", "you swim in a lake", "It's not possible to dance on a lake."], "subject": "lake", "cf_subject": "floor", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Journals can help people in forgetting important events.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Journals can help people in remembering important events.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the function of journals is to help people remember", "Journals are a written record of past experiences to be remembered.", "forgetting important evens is not wanted"], "subject": "forgetting", "cf_subject": "remembering", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"John plays football in outer space.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"John plays football on a field.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Football is never played in outer space.", "People can't breath in outer space, and there is no gravity there, so it's impossible to play football there.", "people cannot live in outer space"], "subject": "in outer space.", "cf_subject": "on a field.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Kids like to sleep with grizzly bears.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Kids like to sleep with teddy bears.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Grizzly bears are dangerous.", "Grizzly bears are dangerous for kids.", "Grizzly bears are dangerous wild animals."], "subject": "grizzly", "cf_subject": "teddy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My brother is awarded a silver medal when he wins the race.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My brother is awarded a gold medal when he wins the race.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Gold medal is given to the winner.", "Silver medals are for second place finishers.", "Winner always gets gold in a sport."], "subject": "silver", "cf_subject": "gold", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He bought groceries at the zoo.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He bought groceries at the store.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Zoo is a place to see animals.", "Groceries aren't sold at the zoo.", "Groceries aren't sold at the zoo."], "subject": "zoo.", "cf_subject": "store.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Orange juice is made of apples\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Orange juice is made of oranges\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Apples' juice comes from apples but not oranges", "Orange juice by definition can only be made with oranges.", "Apples make apple juice, not orange juice."], "subject": "apples", "cf_subject": "oranges", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"my mother switch on the radio to watch movie\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"my mother switch on the television to watch movie\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a radio has no screen to display a movie", "You can't watch a movie on a radio", "Radios have no screens for visual pictures."], "subject": "radio", "cf_subject": "television", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She drove eloquently into the sky.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She danced eloquently into the night.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Anything that can be driven can't go into the sky.", "You cannot drive into the sky, and \"eloquently\" is used to describe speech and writing, not driving.", "Eloquently refers to demeanor of a person not an object."], "subject": "drove sky.", "cf_subject": "danced night.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the sun rises in the west\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the sun rises in the east\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the sun rises in the east and sets in the west", "It depends on the earth position", "The sun always sets in the west"], "subject": "west", "cf_subject": "east", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He played a game with fairies\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He played a game with children\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fairies arent real,  dislike the children", "children are not fairies", "No fairies in the world"], "subject": "fairies", "cf_subject": "children", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My friend runs for 2 inches every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My friend runs for 2 miles every day.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["2 inches is too short a distance to be ran.", "2 inches is not a far distance to run", "2 inches of distance is not enough for a person to run."], "subject": "inches", "cf_subject": "miles", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"sugar is used to make coffee sour\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"sugar is used to make coffee sweet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["sugar usually is used as a sweetener", "Sugar is a sweetening agent.", "Sugar is used to make coffee sweet."], "subject": "sour", "cf_subject": "sweet", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Once a pipe bursts, call a doctor.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Once a pipe bursts, call a plumber.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["plumbers fix the pipes while doctors cure sick people", "Doctors are for people", "Doctors do not specialize in plumbing."], "subject": "doctor.", "cf_subject": "plumber.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The sun sprays water on the planet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The sun shines light on the earth\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The sun emits light not water", "There is no water on the surface of sun", "the sun is super hot"], "subject": "sprays water planet", "cf_subject": "shines light earth", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he was given sweets as he failed the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he was given sweets as he passed the exam\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one celebrates the failure", "failing an exam is not rewarded", "Sweets are happy and exciting, failing an exam is not rewarded."], "subject": "failed", "cf_subject": "passed", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You can use your eyes to eat\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You can use your eyes to see\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People use mouth to eat and eyes to see", "You can use your eyes to see.", "You can't eat through your eyes."], "subject": "eat", "cf_subject": "see", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"in summers, always the weather is cold.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"in summers, always the weather is rainy.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["summers are the hot seasons.", "Usually summer is hot, and winter is cold.", "Normally in summers, the weather is hot"], "subject": "cold.", "cf_subject": "rainy.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The man slipped on the gentle breeze\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man slipped on the banana skin\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is not possible to slip on a gentle breeze for a man", "A gentle breeze will not be on the floor", "A gentle breeze is not slippery."], "subject": "gentle breeze", "cf_subject": "banana skin", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the car in the dog\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the dog in the car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a car is bigger than a dog", "A car would not fit inside a dog.", "A car is a lot bigger than a dog"], "subject": "car dog", "cf_subject": "dog car", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I tied my shoelaces with my shoulders\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I tied my shoelaces with both hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["your shoulders cannot grab shoelaces to tie", "Shoulders are not muscles that have fine motor skills.", "Shoelaces are tired with your fingers."], "subject": "my shoulders", "cf_subject": "both hands", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The bottle drunk out of the baby.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The baby drunk out of the bottle.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The bottle is an object and hasn't lived.", "A baby is not full of consumable fluid.", " a bottle is an inaminate object, so it cannot drink."], "subject": "bottle baby.", "cf_subject": "baby bottle.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he installed the carpet on the lake\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he installed the carpet on the floor\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The carpet will absorb water and sink", "Carpets need a subfloor.", "A lake would not be able to grip onto carpet."], "subject": "lake", "cf_subject": "floor", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the man fed the mouse a snake\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the man fed the snake a mouse\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a mouse can't eat a snake", "mice dont eat snakes", "The mouse is much smaller than the snake"], "subject": "mouse snake", "cf_subject": "snake mouse", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A hole will make a boat float\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A hole will make a boat sink\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A hole will make water fill in the boat and make the boat sink", "A hole will make a boat sink", "You will sink a boat with a hole in it"], "subject": "float", "cf_subject": "sink", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I wear my gloves on my feet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I wear my gloves on my hands.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["gloves are not designed for feet.", "Gloves should be worn on hands instead of feet.", "gloves are meant for hands"], "subject": "feet.", "cf_subject": "hands.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a blue painting is floating in air\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a blue painting hangs on the wall\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["paintings can not float in air", "Gravity does not allow objects such as a painting to stay in the air without falling to the floor.", "a painting cannot float in air, only in water"], "subject": "is floating in air", "cf_subject": "hangs on the wall", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A diet high in sugar is mandatory\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A diet high in sugar is unhealthy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is not mandatory in any country to eat a lot of sugar", "No one can dictate that you must eat a diet high in sugar.", "There is no authority enforcing diets, especially high sugar diets"], "subject": "mandatory", "cf_subject": "unhealthy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Girls are taller than boys on average\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"that girl is taller than that boy\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Boys general grow taller than girls", "Girls and boys vary in height.", "Boys on average are taller than girls"], "subject": "Girls are taller than boys on average", "cf_subject": "that girl is taller than that boy", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Dory moves the desk with her fin.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Dory moves the desk with her arms.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dory does not have fins because she is human.", "People do not have fins.", "Dory lives in the Ocean and does not have a desk"], "subject": "fin.", "cf_subject": "arms.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the little girl howled at the wolf\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A wolf howled at the little girl\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["little girls are sacred when facing a wolf and can not howl", "The wolf would howl at the little girl", "the little girl can scream but not howl at the wolf"], "subject": "the little girl howled at the wolf", "cf_subject": "A wolf howled at the little girl", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"scissors are used to cut through rivers\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"scissors are used to cut through paper\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["scissors cannot cut a liquid", "Scissors are for cutting which cannot be done to water.", " scissors are not used to cut through water."], "subject": "rivers", "cf_subject": "paper", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"surveys have been known to harm children\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"surveys are great to make quick money\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["surveys cannot cause physical harm", "A survey cannot harm a child", "Questions don't harm people...at least not physically"], "subject": "have been known to harm children", "cf_subject": "are great to make quick money", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Roses are blue and violets are red\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Roses are red and violets are blue\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Each flower has a determined color that is very difficult to change naturally", "roses dont come in blue", "The color of roses is usually red, and violets are usually blue."], "subject": "blue red", "cf_subject": "red blue", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He cut the onion with a spoon\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He cut the onion with a knife\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Spoons are too blunt to cut an onion", "Spoon is used to take some foods .", "Spoons are for scooping, not cutting."], "subject": "spoon", "cf_subject": "knife", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He is wearing gloves on his feet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He is wearing gloves on his hands.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["gloves are only designed to wear on hands.", "Gloves are for hands", "gloves go on hands"], "subject": "feet.", "cf_subject": "hands.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She started a fire in the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She started a fire in the fireplace.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["She shouldn't start a fire in the fridge.", "A fire can only be started with heat and friction, and a fridge does not produce heat.", "You couldn't start a fire in a fridge."], "subject": "fridge.", "cf_subject": "fireplace.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"School is where animals go to dance\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"School is where students go to study\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["animals don't go to school", "School is where people go to learn.", "Animals don't go to school."], "subject": "animals dance", "cf_subject": "students study", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"if you want to have a pear then you should go to the toilet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"if you want to have a pee then you should go to the toilet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["there is no pear in the toilet", "Toilets do not have fruits.", "Food is typically not eaten in the bathroom."], "subject": "pear", "cf_subject": "pee", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She made a clown make a shirt\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She made a shirt for a clown\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Clowns don't make shirts for a living", "A shirt  can be made for a clown but a clown cannot be made for a shirt.", "A clown cannot make a shirt"], "subject": "clown make shirt", "cf_subject": "shirt for clown", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Smartphone is a device used for transportation\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Smartphone is a device used for communication\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Smartphone can be only used to communicate, for transportation people usually use automobiles", "A smartphone is a telephone used to talk to people, it does not provide transportation.", "Smartphones are not used for transportation."], "subject": "transportation", "cf_subject": "communication", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The cat drank milk in the duck.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The cat drank milk on the plate.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a cat can not stay in a duck", "Duck are not mammals, so it's impossible to them to produce milk.", "The cat drank milk from the plate  and not from the duck."], "subject": "in duck.", "cf_subject": "on plate.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A grapefruit is bigger than a pumpkin.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A grapefruit is bigger than an orange.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pumpkins are usually bigger than grapefruits.", "a grapefruit is meausured with centimeters, and a pumpkin is measured in inches", "a pumpkin is much bigger than a grapefruit"], "subject": "a pumpkin.", "cf_subject": "an orange.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"People take showers when they feel happy.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"People take showers when they feel dirty.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Showers aren't something related to happiness.", "A show does not affect your emotional state", "People take showers to clean themselves."], "subject": "happy.", "cf_subject": "dirty.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Ripping a paper in half creates six pieces.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Ripping a paper in half creates two pieces.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Half means two relatively equal parts.", "Ripping something in half only allows for 1 more piece than you start with.", "To break something in half always results in only 2 pieces."], "subject": "six", "cf_subject": "two", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"books are used to watch a movie\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"books are used to read and write\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["books can only be used for reading and writing", "books arent needed for movies", "Books cannot play images"], "subject": "watch a movie", "cf_subject": "read and write", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My dog is laying on the ceiling.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My dog is laying on the floor.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Because of gravity, nothing can lay on the ceiling", "Gravity prevents dogs from laying on the ceiling.", "gravity would make them fall off the ceiling"], "subject": "ceiling.", "cf_subject": "floor.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"we go to the disco to pray every weekend\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"we go to the disco to dance every weekend\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["you must pray in quiet places such as churches", "disco is not a holy place", "The disco is for dancing not praying."], "subject": "pray", "cf_subject": "dance", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The man was tired of shoveling marbles every winter.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man was tired of shoveling snow every winter.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Marbles do not fall during winter.", "Marbles do not fall from the sky to be shoveled. This is not a seasonal problem.", "you shovel snow in the winter, not marbles."], "subject": "marbles", "cf_subject": "snow", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You are likely to find a cow in a kennel\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You are likely to find a dog in a kennel\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Cows will always be in farms", "cows are not in kennels", "Dog can be found in a kennel but not cow."], "subject": "cow", "cf_subject": "dog", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman's purse was floating above her.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman's hung purse off her shoulder.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No power to keep the wallet afloat", "A purse is subject to gravity and would not float.", "Unless she is in the water, purses don't float"], "subject": "purse was floating above her.", "cf_subject": "hung purse off her shoulder.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 3, 4, 5, 6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a person with no legs accidentally kicked me in the subway\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a person with no legs accidentally hit me in the subway\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the kick is done through the legs", "to kick it is necessary to have legs", "A person with no legs couldn't kick you."], "subject": "kicked", "cf_subject": "hit", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He parks his car in the closet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He parks his car in the garage.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A car won't fit in the closet.", "The car is too big for the closet", "Closets are not the right place to park cars."], "subject": "closet.", "cf_subject": "garage.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A car engine is usually cooler after driving the car.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A car engine is usually cooler before driving the car.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Driving will cause the engine to be hotter rather than cooler", "An engine becomes hot after driving", "Driving a car heats up the engine."], "subject": "after", "cf_subject": "before", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the generator was able to power the continent\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the generator was able to power the house\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the continent need far more power than a generator can produce", "A continent dosen't require power.", "A generator would not be that powerful."], "subject": "continent", "cf_subject": "house", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Everyday I feed my dog some chocolate bars.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Everyday I feed my dog some dog food.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["If a dog eats chocolate he will die.", "Dogs are given food that is tailored made for them with essential nutrients that they need.", "It is harmful for dogs to eat chocolate"], "subject": "chocolate bars.", "cf_subject": "dog food.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My knee was scrapped and I put dirt on it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My knee was scrapped and I put ointment on it.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Dirt cannot cure or protect the wound.", "One should put ointment on the scrap and not dirt.", "dirt will cause infection"], "subject": "dirt", "cf_subject": "ointment", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"eating trash food every day makes you stronger\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a correct diet is good for your health\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["eating trash food every day makes your body fat and weak", "eating trash food every day is bad for your health", "Trash food could be contaminated"], "subject": "eating trash food every day makes you stronger", "cf_subject": "a correct diet is good for your health", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I put the leftover food in the oven.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I put the leftover food in the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Ovens cannot be used to store food", "Putting food in the oven happens before eating.", "Oven is not for food storing but it is for food cooking."], "subject": "oven.", "cf_subject": "fridge.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a giraffe on the back of his bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he put a person on the back and his bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the giraffe is much bigger than your bike", "A giraffe would be way too big and heavy for the back of his bike.", "Giraffes are too large to fit on the back of a bike."], "subject": "giraffe of", "cf_subject": "person and", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy broke his tooth on a banana pit.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy broke his tooth on a mango pit.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Bananas grow no pits or seeds.", "a banana does not have pits", "bananas dont have pits"], "subject": "banana", "cf_subject": "mango", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy won the race with a cheetah\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy won the race with his friends\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["cheetahs run faster than humans", "The boy can win a race with his friends but not cheetah.", "No human  at any age can win a race with a cheeta which is the fastest land animal on Earth."], "subject": "a cheetah", "cf_subject": "his friends", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My child likes to wear her bathing suit to school.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My child likes to wear her red dress to school.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The bathing suit is not appropriate for school.", "No body goes to school in bathing suit.", "Bathing suit is not appropriate clothing for school."], "subject": "bathing suit", "cf_subject": "red dress", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Japan is the main currency used in Yen.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Yen is the main currency used in Japan.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Japan is not a currency and Yen is not a country.", "people use yen and not countries for payment", "Japan is not a currency."], "subject": "Japan Yen.", "cf_subject": "Yen Japan.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Sweating is a body mechanism to look cool\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Sweating is a body mechanism to cool down\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Sweating is to keep the body temperature down", "Sweating will make the body look red and hot", "Although sweating can look cool, it is not the intended effect of this body mechanism."], "subject": "look cool", "cf_subject": "cool down", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I talked to my friend in the bark.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I talked to my friend in the park.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Bark is either a tree's covering or the sound of a dog.", "It is not physically possible to talk in a bark because a bark is not a place.", "Bark isn't a place you could talk to someone in."], "subject": "bark.", "cf_subject": "park.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the smartphone is a device used for transportation\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the smartphone is a device used for communication\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people usually use automobiles for transportation", "A smartphone is not a machine for transportation.", "Transportation refers to cars, boats, trains, and airplanes."], "subject": "transportation", "cf_subject": "communication", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"a banana contains more water than a watermelon\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"a watermelon contains more water than a banana\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a watermelon usually has higher moisture content than a banana", "Watermelons are mostly water which is why they are called watermelon.", "A watermelon is a storage food for water, and also the size of the watermelon is much bigger in comparison to the banana."], "subject": "banana watermelon", "cf_subject": "watermelon banana", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She went for a run on the Sun.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She went for a run on the trail.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The Sun is too hot to run on.", "It is impossible to run on the sun, it's to hot even to get closer.", "The sun is too far away and too hot to run on."], "subject": "Sun.", "cf_subject": "trail.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He turned on the TV with the VCR.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He turned on the TV with the remote.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["A VCR cannot control a TV's power", "VCR systems are not able to use the TV's power", "The vcr is unable to turn a tv on."], "subject": "VCR.", "cf_subject": "remote.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You can ride the subway in the country.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You can ride the subway in the city.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no subways in the country.", "Subways are underground on a rail system.", "Rural areas don't have subways."], "subject": "country.", "cf_subject": "city.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put the filing cabinet into the papers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put the papers into the filing cabinet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Nothing can be put into the paper.", "it doesnt fit into papers", "The filing cabinet is what papers go into."], "subject": "filing cabinet into the papers.", "cf_subject": "papers into the filing cabinet.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"My sister visited art museum with her zebra\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"My sister visited art museum with her boyfriend\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Animals are forbidden to enter the museum", "Zebras are not allowed in museums", "You can't have a zebra as a pet."], "subject": "zebra", "cf_subject": "boyfriend", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put an ice cream in the oven.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put an ice cream in the freezer.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["if you put ice cream in the oven, it melts.", "that will cause it to melt and no longer be ice cream", "The oven is too hot for ice cream"], "subject": "oven.", "cf_subject": "freezer.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the ice cream in the oven\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she put the ice cream in the freezer\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the ice cream will melt in the oven", "Ice cream would melt in the oven.", "Putting ice cream in the oven would melt it."], "subject": "oven", "cf_subject": "freezer", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the boy fed the fish with a ball\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the boy fed the fish with fish food\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a fish cannot swallow a ball", "The boy fed the fish with fish food and not ball.", "Balls are not edible."], "subject": "a ball", "cf_subject": "fish food", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Spatulas are great for both hiking and fishing.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Spatulas are great for both cooking and baking.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Spatulas have no common uses that would contribute when hiking or fishing.", "You would not use a spatula during outdoors activities.", "Spatulas are not helpful for hiking or fishing."], "subject": "hiking fishing.", "cf_subject": "cooking baking.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He was in the backyard in Minnesota growing some burgers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He was in the backyard in Minnesota grilling some burgers.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["The average person does not grow their burgers.", "Burgers are grilled and not grown.", "One can not grow burgers from the ground."], "subject": "growing", "cf_subject": "grilling", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Reading to your children can make them stronger\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Reading to your children can make them smarter\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["listening to what you read cannot help children to be stronger", "Reading does not make you stronger.", "Reading does not allow one to excercise muscles."], "subject": "stronger", "cf_subject": "smarter", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He combed a bookshelf because it is hairy.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He combed a bookshelf looking for a book.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Bookshelves are not hairy.", "Bookshelves do not need to be combed because books don't have hair.", "bookshelf do not have hair"], "subject": "because it is hairy.", "cf_subject": "looking for a book.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [4, 5, 6, 7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I picked up a basket full of peppers from the tree in the yard.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I picked up a basket full of apples from the tree in the yard.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Pepper is a vegetable that grows in the pepper plant.", "Peppers does not grow in trees.", "Peppers do not grow on trees."], "subject": "peppers", "cf_subject": "apples", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"There are lots of fish in the sky.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"There are lots of fish in the sea.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Fish only live in the water.", "A fish lives in the water only", "Fishes don't live in the sky."], "subject": "sky.", "cf_subject": "sea.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the ice cream stays cold in the microwave\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the ice cream stays cold in the freeze\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["ice cream is not kept in the heat", "The microwave makes food warm", "Icecream stays cool in the fridge and not in microwave."], "subject": "microwave", "cf_subject": "freeze", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he kept the ice cream in the oven\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he kept the ice cream in the fridge\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one keeps ice cream in the oven as it melts", "The ice cream would melt.", "Ice cream melts in the heat."], "subject": "oven", "cf_subject": "fridge", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"you should pull on the brake to accelerate your bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"you should pull on the brake to stop your bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the brake is a restraint used to slow a vehicle", "Brakes are made to increase friction and decrease movement, hence brakes can't accelerate a bike.", "Brakes decelerate a bike, which is the opposite of accelerating it"], "subject": "accelerate", "cf_subject": "stop", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"John can kick the ball with his hands\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"John can kick the ball with his foot\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["KIcking can be done only using foot", "Kicking is an action that is only done with one's feet.", "The ball kicked by foot"], "subject": "hands", "cf_subject": "foot", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She put the contact lens into her mouth\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She put the contact lens into her eye\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Contact lens are used to help you see", "Saliva may contaminate a contact lens with germs.", "Contact lenses are applied to the eyes."], "subject": "mouth", "cf_subject": "eye", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"i am going are computer buy on mobile shop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"i am going are computer buy on Acer store\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["mobile shop is an only mobile sale", "You buy computers at computer shops.", "You purchase computers at computer stores, not mobile shops."], "subject": "mobile shop", "cf_subject": "Acer store", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy wore his new shoes on his back.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The boy wore his new shoes on his feet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one wears shoes on their backs.", "A person is not able to wear shoes on their back.", "Shoes are worn on your feet not your back."], "subject": "back.", "cf_subject": "feet.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"the owner of the restaurant apologized for the good customer service\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"the owner of the restaurant apologized for the terrible customer service\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["good customer service isn't a fault, so no one should apologize for it", "you wouldn't apologize for good service.", "Apology is for bad customer service and not good customer service."], "subject": "good", "cf_subject": "terrible", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"It is easy to find seashells in the forest\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"It is easy to find seashells by the ocean\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["seashells don't grow on trees", "Seashells are made from living things of coean only", "Seashells exist by the sea"], "subject": "in forest", "cf_subject": "by ocean", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You are more likely to overeat on a full stomach.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You are more likely to overeat on an empty stomach.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You can hardly eat anything if your stomach is already full", "If your stomach is full, there will be less room for food", "You will stop eating on a full stomach"], "subject": "a full", "cf_subject": "an empty", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"When people cry,  tears come out of their ears\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"When people cry,  tears come out of their eyes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no tear ducting in ears", "Tears come from tearducts in the eye and so the tears can't come out of a person's ears.", "tears come out of eyes"], "subject": "ears", "cf_subject": "eyes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The child studied a lot to open a door.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The child studied a lot to take a test.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Opening a door isn't something you study for.", "You don't need to study to open a door.", "It doesn't really require study to learn how to open a door."], "subject": "open door.", "cf_subject": "take test.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Jimmy got his leg bitten off by a kitten\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Jimmy got his leg bitten off by a shark\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a kitten's teeth are not that sharp", "Kittens are too small to effectively dismember a person.", "Kittens can not bite a person's leg off."], "subject": "kitten", "cf_subject": "shark", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"A neighbor is a person who lives far from you\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"A neighbor is a person who lives next to you\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people live near to each other are called neighbor", "A neighbor must live near you", "a neighbor lives next to your house"], "subject": "far from", "cf_subject": "next to", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Something that might happen while bathing is your shirt becomes wet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Something that might happen while bathing is your body becomes wet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["While bathing we will removes our clothes including shirts", "because if our goal is to bathe, best way is the bath  without  shirt", "people take of their clothes when they bathe"], "subject": "shirt", "cf_subject": "body", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I sliced the strong meat with my Kitchen spoon.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I sliced the strong meat with my Kitchen Knife.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Spoons are not used for slicing food like a knife.", "Spoons are not sharp enough to cut meat.", "Spoons are used for scooping."], "subject": "spoon.", "cf_subject": "Knife.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He closed the blinds because it was too dark\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He closed the blinds because it was too bright\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Blinds are used to reduce brightness, if it is dark then it should be opened", "You would open the blinds if it was too dark.", "Closing the blinds would make it less bright."], "subject": "dark", "cf_subject": "bright", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she went to buy a toothbrush at a flower shop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she went to buy a toothbrush at a petty shop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["flower shop won't sell a toothbrush", "there are no toothbrushes at the flower shop", "Flower shop sells flowers not toothbrushes."], "subject": "flower", "cf_subject": "petty", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"hair gel is to be applied onto the back\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"hair gel is to be applied onto the scalp\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["hair gel is usually used on the head", "You apply hair geltoyour hair.", "back we apply pain relief"], "subject": "back", "cf_subject": "scalp", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he gave his dresses to wash in the study room\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he gave his dresses to wash in the laundry room\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["no one is to wash our dresses in the study room, it used to study.", "The study room is for studying and not laundry", "There are no washing machines in the study room."], "subject": "study", "cf_subject": "laundry", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Jim went to watch a movie at the gym\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Jim went to watch a movie at the theater\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no movies to watch in the gym", "No projector to watch the movie at gym", "there are no movies at the gym"], "subject": "gym", "cf_subject": "theater", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"If you need water, get it from the oven.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"IF you need water, get it from the sink.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There is no water in the oven.", "Can't get water from an oven.", "You can't get water from an oven."], "subject": "If oven.", "cf_subject": "IF sink.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [0, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He went to the theater for a medical checkup\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He went to the theater to watch a movie\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Medical checkup is usually done in hospitals", "Theater is not the place for medical checkup", "there are no doctors there"], "subject": "for a medical checkup", "cf_subject": "to watch a movie", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 6, 7, 8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"he sent me a text message from his ashtray\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"he sent me a text message from his smartphone\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["ashtrays are not electronic devices", "Ashtrays do not have a texting feature.", "Ashtrays are used to put ash in and not to send messages."], "subject": "ashtray", "cf_subject": "smartphone", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"When people cry, tears come out of their ears\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"When people cry, tears come out of their eyes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["There are no tear ducts in ears", "Tears come out of a person's eyes, not their ears.", "tears come out of eyes"], "subject": "ears", "cf_subject": "eyes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I swam to the lowest point of the ocean in one breath\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I swam to the lowest point of the pool in one breath\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People are not strong enough to swim to the lowest point of the ocean", "The pressure of the water would crush you before you got to the bottom of the ocean", "The ocean is too deep for people to get to the bottom."], "subject": "ocean", "cf_subject": "pool", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I need to heat up some water using the refrigerator\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I need to heat up some water using the microwave\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["refrigerators have low temperatures", "You can't heat anything in a refrigerator.", "refrigerator makes cool"], "subject": "refrigerator", "cf_subject": "microwave", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"I am going for my family tour in one cycle\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"I am going for my family tour on one bus\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["only one person to travel per one cycle", "the family does not fit into a cycle", "Going for a family tour would involve more than one person and a cycle is for one person."], "subject": "in cycle", "cf_subject": "on bus", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He went to fishing in the Jeep to the desert.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He went for fishing in the boat to the lake.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["fishing can be done on the lake only.", "You wouldn't go fishing in a desert where there's no water.", "Fishing is done at the sea not the desert."], "subject": "to Jeep desert.", "cf_subject": "for boat lake.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [2, 6, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Wallets are typically used to hold spider eggs and denim.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Wallets are typically used to hold cash and credit cards.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Wallets are used for financial security.", "Wallets are meant to store cash and cards, not insects or fabric", "Wallets are meant for the purpose of holding currency."], "subject": "spider eggs and denim.", "cf_subject": "cash and credit cards.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7, 8, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The man who flies a plane is called a conductor.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The man who flies a plane is called the captain.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Conductors operate trains.", "Pilots fly planes.", "The man who flies a plane called a captain."], "subject": "a conductor.", "cf_subject": "the captain.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman had her hair cut at the hardware store.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"The woman had her hair cut at the hair salon.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Hardware stores don't cut people's hair.", "Haircuts happen at salons.", "Hardware stores sell hardware, they do not provide hair cuts"], "subject": "hardware store.", "cf_subject": "hair salon.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [8, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You are likely to find Rice bags in shoe shops\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You are likely to find sandals in a shoe shop\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Rice bags will be available in Grocery shops rather than shoe shops", "Shoe shops do not sell rice bags.", "Rice bags are found in grocery shops not shoe shops."], "subject": "Rice bags in shops", "cf_subject": "sandals in a shop", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 6, 7, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"if you want fresh fruits and vegetables, you should destroy them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"if you want fresh fruits and vegetables, you should grow them\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["you will get nothing after destroying the fruits and vegetables", "you can't have something that has been destroyed", "Destroying fruits and vegetables negates the want."], "subject": "destroy", "cf_subject": "grow", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"You will probably find a front condo in a room.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"You will probably find a front room in a condominium.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Condos are made up of bedrooms which will likely have a front room", "A condo is much bigger than a living room.", "A condo doesn't fit in a room."], "subject": "condo room.", "cf_subject": "room condominium.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He broke his leg and went to get a burger\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He broke his leg and had to get a cast\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["He would be in too much pain For a burger", "broken legs require being hospitalized", "He broke a leg and had to make a dressing and did not go to get a hamburger because his loss was broken"], "subject": "went burger", "cf_subject": "had cast", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [5, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Joe asked Mary to have a date because he dislikes her\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Joe asked Mary to have a date because he likes her\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["People will only ask people they like out for a date", "if someones asking someone to go on a date, they like them.", "Joe wouldn't want to go on a date with Mary if he disliked her because it wouldn't be enjoyable."], "subject": "dislikes", "cf_subject": "likes", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"you are supposed to buy tickets after you get off the train\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"you are supposed to buy tickets before you get on the train\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["the rule is to buy tickets first and then take the train", "You are supposed to buy tickets before you get on the train", "You are supposed to buy tickets before you get on the train"], "subject": "after off", "cf_subject": "before on", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"To get to the top of the building you must use an elevator\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"To get to the top of the building you may use an elevator\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["I can get to the top of the building using the stairs", "You could also use the stairs.", "There are stairs to the top."], "subject": "must", "cf_subject": "may", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Some people like to put a scarf around their ears.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Some people like to put a scarf around their necks.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["You can't put a scarf around an ear.", "An ear isn't big enough to hold a scarf.", "A scarf is much larger than an ear, and probably would not fasten around it."], "subject": "ears.", "cf_subject": "necks.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"She continued watching TV as she urinated in her pants.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"She went to the bathroom to urinate in the toilet.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["It is unsanitary and can be harmful to the skin to sit in urine-soaked clothes.", "Watching TV will not cause for urination.", "that is not where you are suppose to pee"], "subject": "continued watching TV as she urinated her pants.", "cf_subject": "went to the bathroom to urinate the toilet.", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 8, 9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she wants to drink some water because she is full\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she wants to drink some water because she is thirsty\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["people always don't drink water when they are full", "When people are full they do not want to fill their stomachs more.", "She won't have room in her stomach for anything if she's full."], "subject": "full", "cf_subject": "thirsty", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [9]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Mike went to the grocery store three blocks away by plane\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Mike went to the grocery store three blocks away by bike\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["Three blocks' distance is too short for taking a plane", "A plane can only fly in the sky", "MIKE WENT TO THE GROCERY STORE THREE BLOCKS AWAY BY CAR"], "subject": "plane", "cf_subject": "bike", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [10]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"He sent some messages from the WhatsApp mobile application by his shoes\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"He sent some messages from the WhatsApp mobile application by his mobile\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one can send the WhatsApp messages by their's shoes.", "Shoes cant send messages of any kind", "A mobile application exist on a mobile phone, it is not a physical object."], "subject": "shoes", "cf_subject": "mobile", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [11]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"she was met with an accident and was rushed to the library\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"she was met with an accident and was rushed to the hospital\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["a library is full of books without doctors and nurses", "Libraries are a non-emergency service.", "She was in an accident and going to the library would make her injuries worse, if not fatal."], "subject": "library", "cf_subject": "hospital", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [11]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Anthony decided that he will kick the warm glass of water to the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Anthony concluded that he will put the warm glass of water in the fridge.\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["kicking a glass of water will make the glass falls and the water spills", "Kicking a glass of water will tip it over and damage the fridge", "Kicking glasd would cause it to break and it would not make it to the fridge."], "subject": "decided kick to", "cf_subject": "concluded put in", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [1, 5, 11]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"If you want to have a party then you should invite things\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"If you want to have a party then you should invite guests\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["To hold a party,  you have to invite guests rather than things", "Things cannot be invited to a party, they are brought to a party by the invited guests", "In a party one can invite guests and not things."], "subject": "things", "cf_subject": "guests", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [11]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"dogs are social animals who prefer a solitary existence to live in a pack\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"dogs are social animals who prefer life in a pack to a solitary existence\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["dogs prefer interacting with others and do not cope well alone", "Dogs cannot be social  and require solitary existence, social is the exact of solitary.", "If dogs are social animals, they can not also prefer a solitary existence."], "subject": "a solitary existence to live in a pack", "cf_subject": "life in a pack to a solitary existence", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"if it doesn't rain for a long time, the earth will get very wet\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"if it doesn't rain for a long time, the earth will get very dry\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["earth won't get wet if there is no rain", "If it didn't rain for a long time to earth would be dry", "The earth experiences a drought without rain."], "subject": "wet", "cf_subject": "dry", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [13]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"Toothbrush is a small brush with a long handle, used for cleaning the car\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"Toothbrush is a small brush with a long handle, used for cleaning the teeth\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["usually people clean their teeth using a toothbrush", "Toothbrush is a small brush with a long handle, used for cleaning the teeth", "It would take too long to try to clean a car with a toothbrush"], "subject": "car", "cf_subject": "teeth", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [13]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"dogs are very social animals who prefer a solitary existence to live in a pack\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"dogs are very social animals who prefer life in a pack to a solitary existence\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["social animals prefer interacting with others and do not cope well alone", "Social animals such as dogs do not prefer a solitary life.", "a solitary existence is being alone and not surrounded by others"], "subject": "a solitary existence to live in a pack", "cf_subject": "life in a pack to a solitary existence", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14]}
{"question": "Given this sentence: \"If you want to buy presents for others then you should figure out what you want\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "cf_question": "Given this sentence: \"If you want to buy presents for others then you should figure out what they want\" . Is this sentence against common sense?", "choices": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": "A", "correct_explanation": ["No one buys gifts they want to give that to others", "In buying presents we should figure out what they want and not what we want.", "If you are buying presents for others you shouldn't get what you want, instead get what they want."], "subject": "you", "cf_subject": "they", "cf_answer": "B", "subject_range": [14]}
